1.	O
EDUCATION	O
•	O
Graduated	B-DEGREE
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
•	O
Vice	O
President	O
of	O
Student	B-ORG
Union	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Hanoi	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
•	O
Training	O
Institute:	O
Electronics	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Telecommunications	I-ORG
•	O
Research	O
majors:	O
AI,	B-MAJOR
Data	I-MAJOR
science	I-MAJOR
.	O

-	O
Github	O
link:	O
https://github.com/huy26/Manual-NN-Mushroom-Classifier-using-3-hidden-layers	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
Project:	O
-	O
Project	O
Scope:	O
Worked	O
as	O
part	O
of	O
five-member	O
team	O
to	O
model	O
and	O
train	O
a	O
convolutional	O
neural	O
network	O
on	O
artificial	O
datasets	O
versus	O
train	O
on	O
real	O
datasets.	O
Create	O
FACADE	O
(Fully	O
Algorithmic	O
and	O
Complete	O
Artificial	B-TECH_SKILL
Drawing	I-TECH_SKILL
Engine	I-TECH_SKILL
)	O
to	O
generate	O
artificial	O
hand-drawn	O
polygons	O
and	O
MNIST-like	O
set	O
of	O
hand-drawn	O
digits.	O
Use	O
those	O
artificial	O
data	O
to	O
train	O
on	O
LeNet-5	B-TECH_SKILL
architecture	O
and	O
compare	O
with	O
real	O
dataset.	O
Use	O
YOLO	B-TECH_SKILL
v3	O
and	O
v4	O
along	O
with	O
Darknet	B-TECH_SKILL
to	O
see	O
if	O
artificially	O
generated	O
polygons	O
can	O
be	O
localized	O
in	O
the	O
image.	O
-	O
Tools:	O
Jupiter	B-TECH_SKILL
notebook	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Google	B-TECH_SKILL
Colab	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Sep	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Applied	O
Mathematics	O
and	O
Informatics	O
Major:	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
-	I-MAJOR
Informatics	I-MAJOR
GPA	O
2020.2:	O
4.0	O
CPA:	B-SCORE
3.40	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
2019-2023	B-TIME
Currently	O
a	O
third-year	O
student	O
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
Department.	O
Tran	B-ORG
Dai	I-ORG
Nghia	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
2016-2019	B-TIME
Mathematically	B-MAJOR
Specialized	O
Class	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Arti�cial	B-MAJOR
Intelligence	I-MAJOR
|	O
FPT	B-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
Sep	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
100%	O
Scholarship	O
GPA	B-SCORE
8.86	I-SCORE
Google	O
Data	O
Analytics	O
COURSERA	O
|	O
May	B-TIME
2022	I-TIME
-	O
No	O
expire	O
date	O
Ability	O
to	O
perform	O
data	O
cleaning,	O
organizing,	O
and	O
visualizing.	O
Get	O
familiar	O
with	O
tools	O
for	O
Data	O
Analytics	O
like	O
spreadsheets	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tableau	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
and	O
R	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
Florida	I-ORG
Tampa	I-ORG
,	O
FL	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science	I-DEGREE
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
Expected	O
Graduation:	O
2025	B-TIME
GPA:	B-SCORE
4.0	I-SCORE
Related	O
Coursework:	O
Calculus,	O
Programming	O
Concepts,	O
Discrete	O
Structure	O
Udemy	O
courses:	O
Mathematics	O
Foundation	O
of	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
A-Z	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
AND	O
TRAINING	O
08/2021	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
01/2022	I-TIME
–	O
Uppsala	B-ORG
,	O
Sweden	B-LOC
EXCHANGE	O
STUDENT	O
OF	O
ERASMUS	O
+	O
KEY	O
ACTION	O
1	O
PROGRAM	O
–	O
Uppsala	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Main	O
subject	O
/	O
occupational	O
skills	O
covered:	O
Basic	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
and	O
Data	O
Mining:	O
Data	O
preprocessing,	O
Association	O
Rules,	O
etc.	O
Basic	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Artiﬁcial	O
Intelligence:	O
Search	B-TECH_SKILL
Algorithms	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Markov	B-TECH_SKILL
Chain	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Bayes	B-TECH_SKILL
Networks	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
etc.	O
◦	O
Basic	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Human-Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Interaction	I-TECH_SKILL
◦	O
Enhance	O
collaborative	O
working	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
partnerships	O
◦	O
Field(s)	O
of	O
study	O
◦	O
Information	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Communication	I-MAJOR
Technologies	I-MAJOR
◦	O
08/2019	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
CURRENT	I-TIME
–	O
1,	B-LOC
Dai	I-LOC
Co	I-LOC
Viet	I-LOC
Street,	I-LOC
Hanoi,	I-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
STUDENT	O
SPECIALIZING	O
IN	O
ICT	O
PROGRAM	O
–	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Main	O
subject	O
/	O
occupational	O
skills	O
covered:	O
Understand	O
basic	O
data	O
structures	O
and	O
algorithms.	O
Understand	O
fundamental	O
theories	O
about	O
Operating	B-TECH_SKILL
systems	I-TECH_SKILL
(OS),	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Network	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Object	O
◦	O
Oriented	B-TECH_SKILL
Programming	I-TECH_SKILL
(OOP),	O
etc.	O
◦	O
Actively	O
collaborate	O
with	O
partners	O
to	O
make	O
progress	O
in	O
learning.	O
Field(s)	O
of	O
study	O
◦	O
Information	O
and	O
Communication	O
Technologies	O
◦	O
https://www.hust.edu.vn/	O
01/2019	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
01/2021	I-TIME
–	O
20,	B-LOC
Thuy	I-LOC
Khue	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
,	I-LOC
Hanoi,	I-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
IELTS	O
6.0	O
–	O
British	B-ORG
Council	I-ORG
.	O

Programming	O
•	O
Programming	O
Language:	O
familiar	O
with:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C/C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
LaTeX	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
HTML/CSS	B-TECH_SKILL
•	O
Frameworks,	O
Libraries	O
familiar	O
with:	O
tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
•	O
Tools	O
and	O
the	O
others:	O
Git	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Docker	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

W	O
O	O
R	O
K	O
E	O
X	O
P	O
E	O
R	O
I	O
E	O
N	O
C	O
E	O
S	O
SAMSUNG	B-ORG
VIETNAM	I-ORG
MOBILE	I-ORG
R&D	I-ORG
CENTER	I-ORG
7/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
8/2020	I-TIME
Internship	B-POSITION
Learning	O
about	O
Data	O
structures	O
and	O
Algorithms	O
Learning	O
about	O
Java	O
Android	O
Completing	O
the	O
Programming	O
Test	O
with	O
100/100	O
VIN	B-ORG
BIG	I-ORG
DATA	I-ORG
-	O
AI	B-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
10/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
10/2021	I-TIME
Completing	O
the	O
AI	O
training	O
course	O
Join	O
HateSpeech	O
Detection	O
task	O
in	O
Virtual	O
Assistant	O
VIVI	O
Collect,	O
processing,	O
evaluate	O
data.	O
Implement	O
Classi�cation	O
model	O
(	O
BERT	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
LSTM	B-TECH_SKILL
,...).	O
Deploy	O
detect	O
Hate	O
Speech	O
tool	O
in	O
Web	O
Application.	O
Join	O
Message	O
Extractiọn	O
task	O
in	O
Virtual	O
Assistant	O
VIVI	O
Generate,	O
processing	O
data	O
Fine-tuining	O
Message	O
Extraction	O
models	O
Implement	O
rule-based,	O
post-processing	O
Deploy	O
system	O
extraction	O
in	O
Android	O
Application.	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Vaasa,	B-ORG
Finland	I-ORG
VAMK,	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Applied	I-ORG
Sciences	I-ORG
May	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
•	O
BEng	B-DEGREE
in	O
Information	B-MAJOR
Technology,	I-MAJOR
Software	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
major,	O
Telecommunication	O
minor	O
•	O
Overall	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
4.6/5.0	I-SCORE
,	O
1	O
of	O
5	O
top-notch	O
students	O
in	O
class	O
•	O
Relevant	O
Coursework:	O
Linear	O
Algebra	O
&	O
Calculus,	O
Databases	O
&	O
Open	O
Interfaces,	O
Linux	B-TECH_SKILL
OS	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
OOP	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
LAN	B-TECH_SKILL
&	I-TECH_SKILL
WAN	I-TECH_SKILL
Hanoi,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
HNUE,	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
Students	I-ORG
August	B-TIME
2015	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
May	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
•	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Sciences	I-MAJOR
Specialization,	O
Overall	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.0/10.0	I-SCORE
•	O
Relevant	O
Coursework:	O
Algorithms	O
and	O
Data	O
Structures	O
•	O
Awards	O
&	O
Honors:	O
Reserved	O
Team	O
of	O
National	O
Olympiad	O
in	O
Computer	O
Science	O
•	O
Extracurricular	O
Activities:	O
Best	O
Picture	O
in	O
school’s	O
short	O
film	O
making	O
competition	O
.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Techainer	B-ORG
�	O
Aug	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Dec	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
�	O
Ha	B-LOC
Noi	I-LOC
•	O
Iteratively	O
generated	O
synthetic	O
data	O
and	O
helped	O
in	O
training	O
detection/classiﬁcation	O
DNNs	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
Incoming	O
Software	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
,	O
AthenaHealth	B-ORG
Jun	B-TIME
2022	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
·	O
Contributing	O
to	O
Practice	O
Management	O
and	O
Collector	O
Tools	O
products.	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
Graduate	O
Research	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
,	O
Northeastern	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Mar	B-TIME
2022	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
·	O
Implemented	O
Deep	O
Learning	O
models	O
(	O
FlowNet	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
RAFT	B-TECH_SKILL
)	O
to	O
estimate	O
optical	O
ﬂow	O
in	O
sports	O
video.	O
Developed	O
models	O
to	O
interpolate	O
intermediate	O
frames	O
and	O
generate	O
slow	O
motion	O
videos.	O
Computational	B-POSITION
Biologist	I-POSITION
,	O
Singapore	B-ORG
Bioinformatics	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
Jun	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
·	O
Developed	O
novel	O
high-dimensional	O
statistical	O
analysis	O
deployed	O
on	O
Google	B-TECH_SKILL
Cloud	I-TECH_SKILL
Platform	I-TECH_SKILL
web	O
app	O
with	O
R-Shiny	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
HTML	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

•	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Researcher	B-POSITION
School	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Applied	I-ORG
Mathematics	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Informatics	I-ORG
–	I-ORG
HUST	I-ORG
09/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
•	O
Learn	O
about	O
segmentation	O
problems,	O
speciﬁcally	O
applied	O
to	O
the	O
problem	O
of	O
extracting	O
building	O
footprint	O
boundaries	O
through	O
remote	O
sensing	O
images	O
•	O
Using	O
EEM	O
data	O
to	O
solve	O
the	O
problem	O
of	O
determining	O
chemical	O
concentrations	O
in	O
the	O
Han	O
River’s	O
water	O
Learn	O
how	O
to	O
write	O
a	O
paper	O
and	O
work	O
with	O
the	O
research	O
team	O
under	O
the	O
guidance	O
of	O
the	O
instructor	O
•	O
Python	B-POSITION
Tutor	I-POSITION
Freelancer	O
11/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
08/2021	I-TIME
•	O
Tutored	O
basic	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Data	O
Structures	O
&	O
Algorithms	O
for	O
8th	O
graders	O
Data	B-POSITION
Science	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Viettel	B-ORG
Digital	I-ORG
Service	I-ORG
09/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
12/2020	I-TIME
•	O
Developed	O
credit	O
scoring	O
model	O
with	O
0.8	O
ROC	O
-	O
AUC	O
scores	O
using	O
Viettel’s	O
telecommunications	O
data	O
Learned	O
Time	O
Series	O
Data	O
to	O
preprocessing	O
telecommunications	O
data	O
•	O
.	O

EDUCATIONAL	O
BACKGROUND	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Major:	O
Data	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
.	O

Gained	O
overall	O
88%	O
accuracy.	O
(Poster)	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
9/2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
Final	O
year	O
student	O
–	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
Nguyen	B-ORG
Tat	I-ORG
Thanh	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
09/2015	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
05/2018	I-TIME
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCES	O
MACHINE	B-POSITION
LEARNING	I-POSITION
TEACHER	I-POSITION
ASSISTANT	I-POSITION
CODERSCHOOL	B-ORG
,	O
July	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
Responsible	O
for	O
helping	O
Instructor	O
in	O
Machine	O
learning/	O
Data	O
Analyst	O
courses	O
-	O
Handling,	O
debugging	O
students'	O
final	O
project	O
products;	O
-	O
Delivering	O
lectures	O
on	O
fundamental	O
topics	O
of	O
programming	O
and	O
machine	O
learning.	O
DIGITAL	B-POSITION
MARKETING	I-POSITION
EXECUTIVE	I-POSITION
REEPRO	B-ORG
SOLAR	I-ORG
,	O
Oct	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Mar	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Responsible	O
for	O
establishing	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
company's	O
digital	O
assets:	O
-Building	O
and	O
maintaining	O
the	O
company	O
website:	O
www.reeprosolar.com;	O
-	O
Optimize	O
website	O
SEO	O
and	O
establishing	O
digital	O
analytic	O
tools	O
to	O
track	O
website	O
data;	O
-	O
Collaborate	O
with	O
content	O
writer	O
and	O
designer	O
to	O
attract	O
site	O
traffic;	O
-	O
Establishing	O
company	O
profiles	O
on	O
social	O
and	O
other	O
digital	O
channels:	O
Linkedin,	O
Google	O
My	O
Bussiness,	O
Zalo	O
Official	O
Account,...;	O
.	O

NGUYEN	B-NAME
LAM	I-NAME
NGUYEN	I-NAME
Mobile:	O
0901436282	B-PHONE
Email:	O
nguyennl1108@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
Date	O
of	O
Birth:	O
11/8/2001	O
Gender:	O
Male	O
Address:	O
89	B-LOC
Nguyen	I-LOC
Thai	I-LOC
Son	I-LOC
street,	I-LOC
Go	I-LOC
Vap	I-LOC
district,	I-LOC
Ho	I-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
city,	I-LOC
VietNam	I-LOC
.	O

Education	O
2018	B-TIME
,	O
B.Sc	B-DEGREE
Information	B-MAJOR
Technology	I-MAJOR
,	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
2018	B-TIME
,	O
Autumn	O
School	O
of	O
Development	O
,	O
iSEE	O
2020,	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
Integrity	B-ORG
School	I-ORG
,	I-ORG
Towards	I-ORG
Transparency	I-ORG
.	O

.	O

Participating	O
in	O
weekly	O
planning	O
meetings.	O
AI	B-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
VNP	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
11/2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
04/2020	I-TIME
,	O
Hanoi,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
Viet	O
Nam	O
Price	O
Joint	O
Stock	O
Company	O
Achievements/Tasks	O
Data	O
preprocessing	O
(clean	O
data,	O
label	O
data,	O
crawl	O
data).	O
Building	O
application	O
to	O
extract	O
information	O
from	O
documents.	O
Developing	O
microservices	O
with	O
Flask.	O
Contributing	O
to	O
NER	B-TECH_SKILL
model	O
for	O
CV	O
extraction	O
project.	O
Participating	O
in	O
weekly	O
planning	O
meetings.	O
.	O

.	O

GENERAL	O
SKILL	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
Deep	I-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
Natural	I-TECH_SKILL
Language	I-TECH_SKILL
Processing	I-TECH_SKILL
Big	I-TECH_SKILL
data	I-TECH_SKILL
Data	I-TECH_SKILL
Visualization	I-TECH_SKILL
Data	I-TECH_SKILL
Structures	I-TECH_SKILL
&	I-TECH_SKILL
Algorithms	I-TECH_SKILL
Data	O
Preparation	O
Research	O
&	O
Analysis	O
Critical	B-SOFT_SKILL
Thinking	I-SOFT_SKILL
Teamwork	I-SOFT_SKILL
Leadership	I-SOFT_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
HANOI	B-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
OF	I-ORG
SCIENCE	I-ORG
(HUS)	I-ORG
Fall	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Summer	I-TIME
2023	I-TIME
(Expected)	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science	I-DEGREE
-	O
Talented	O
Program	O
Major:	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
Current	I-MAJOR
Cummulative	I-MAJOR
:	O
3.1	O
Course	O
Hightlights:	O
Linear	O
Algebra,	O
Abstract	O
Algebra,	O
Calculus,	O
Advance	O
Calculus,	O
Probability	O
&	O
Statistics,	O
Discrete	O
Math,	O
Topology,	O
Numerical	O
Analysic,	O
Functional	O
Analysic,	O
Ordinary	O
Differential	O
Equations,	O
Partial	O
Differential	O
Equations,	O
Optimization,	O
System	O
and	O
Control	O
Theory,	O
Applied	O
Statistic.	O
RESEARCH	O
INTERESTS	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
,	O
Deep	O
Learning,	O
Optimization,	O
Algorithms,	O
Modeling,	O
Control	O
System.	O
.	O

-	O
Build	O
a	O
backend	O
using	O
PHP	B-TECH_SKILL
(core).	O
Movie	O
Review	O
Application	O
Technologies:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Define	O
the	O
requirements	O
of	O
the	O
project.	O
-	O
Research	O
and	O
integrate	O
the	O
recommendation	O
system	O
into	O
the	O
backend.	O
Chat	O
Application	O
Technologies:	O
ReactJS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Express	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
NodeJS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
MongoDB	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Build	O
chat	O
web	O
application	O
Data	O
Conversion	O
Tool	O
(Graduation	O
Thesis)	O
Technologies:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
MySQL	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
MongoDB	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Docker	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Build	O
a	O
tool	O
that	O
converts	O
data	O
from	O
Relational	O
Database	O
(	O
MySQL	B-TECH_SKILL
)	O
to	O
NoSQL	B-TECH_SKILL
(	O
MongoDB	B-TECH_SKILL
)	O
.	O

Education	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
and	O
2019-2023	B-TIME
Technology	O
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
GPA:	O
8.0	B-SCORE
I'm	O
studying	O
3rd	O
year	O
university.	O
.	O

ML	O
Algorithms:	O
Linear	B-TECH_SKILL
Reg	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Logistic	B-TECH_SKILL
Reg	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tree,	O
Ensemble	B-TECH_SKILL
Tree	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Naive	B-TECH_SKILL
Bayes	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SVM	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
K-NN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
K-Means	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
DBSCAN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
DNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
CNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Anomaly	O
De-	O
tection,	O
FP-Growth.	O
Skills:	O
transfer	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
read	O
metrics	O
(accuracy,	O
precision,	O
recall,	O
F1,	O
.	O

SKILLS	O
Problem-solving	B-SOFT_SKILL
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
Algorithms	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
Data	O
structure	O
Teamwork	B-SOFT_SKILL
Spark	B-TECH_SKILL
Communication	B-SOFT_SKILL
Research	O
.	O

RESEARCH	O
AND	O
WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Computational	B-ORG
Biomedicine	I-ORG
Department,	I-ORG
Vingroup	I-ORG
Big	I-ORG
Data	I-ORG
Institute	I-ORG
December	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Current	I-TIME
Research	B-POSITION
collaborator	I-POSITION
•	O
Supervisor:	O
Assoc.	O
Prof.	O
Duc-Hau	O
Le,	O
MS.	O
Trang	O
Tran	O
Thi	O
Ha.	O
•	O
Studying	O
problems	O
in	O
computational	O
biomedicine.	O
•	O
Applying	O
statistical	O
and	O
machine	O
learning	O
methods	O
to	O
solve	O
bioinformatics	O
problems,	O
focusing	O
on	O
cancer	O
subtyping/classification	O
using	O
biomedical	O
data	O
and	O
predicting	O
the	O
risk	O
of	O
genetic	O
diseases.	O
Data	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
Laboratory,	I-ORG
SOICT,	I-ORG
HUST	I-ORG
April	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Current	I-TIME
Research	B-POSITION
student	I-POSITION
•	O
Supervisor:	O
Assoc.	O
Prof.	O
Khoat	O
Than,	O
MS.	O
Linh	O
Ngo	O
Van.	O
•	O
Studying	O
basic	O
and	O
advanced	O
knowledge	O
in	O
machine	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
especially	O
statistical	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
continual	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
contrastive	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
etc.	O
•	O
Applying	O
state-of-the-art	O
methods	O
published	O
in	O
scientific	O
papers	O
to	O
real-world	O
problems.	O
AI	B-ORG
Department,	I-ORG
VNP	I-ORG
Group	I-ORG
December	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
March	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
•	O
Developing	O
computer	O
vision	O
techniques	O
(e.g.,	O
character	O
recognition	O
and	O
face	O
recognition)	O
and	O
applying	O
them	O
in	O
some	O
products	O
of	O
VNP	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
VNU	I-ORG
HCMUS	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2024	I-TIME
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science	I-DEGREE
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
.	O

​	O
NGUYEN	B-NAME
TIEN	I-NAME
THUAN	I-NAME
Ha	B-LOC
Noi,	I-LOC
Viet	I-LOC
Nam	I-LOC
	O
0396295196	B-PHONE
	O
thuannhoden5@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
	O
https://github.com/thuannhoden5	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering	I-DEGREE
,	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Aug	B-TIME
2016	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
BE	B-DEGREE
in	O
Electronics	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Telecommunications	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
(Talent	O
Program)	O
Aug	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
CPA:	B-SCORE
3.22/4.0	I-SCORE
(8.05/10)	O
Thesis	O
title:	O
“A	O
glove-based	O
gesture	O
recognition	O
system	O
for	O
Vietnamese	O
sign	O
language,	O
using	O
the	O
ProtoNN	B-TECH_SKILL
algorithm	O
on	O
a	O
resource-scarce	O
device	O
(Arduino	O
Uno”	O
Degree	O
Classification:	O
Very	O
good	O
.	O

Employment	O
History	O
Intern	B-POSITION
AI	I-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
,	O
I3	B-ORG
Automation	I-ORG
,	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
APRIL	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
JUNE	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Worked	O
well	O
independently	O
and	O
on	O
a	O
team	O
to	O
solve	O
problems	O
Create	O
a	O
sub-module	O
for	O
detecting	O
face-liveness	O
.	O

.	O

�EDUCATION	O
Aug	B-TIME
2016	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
�	O
HANOI	B-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
OF	I-ORG
SCIENCE	I-ORG
AND	I-ORG
TECHNOLOGY	I-ORG
(HUST)	I-ORG
Major:	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
And	I-MAJOR
Informatics	I-MAJOR
(Talent	O
Program)	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.34/4.00	I-SCORE
.	O

INTERNSHIP	B-POSITION
EXPERIENCE	O
Texas	B-ORG
A&M	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
August	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Graduate	O
Teaching	O
Assistant	O
(GAT)	O
in	O
the	O
Department	O
of	O
Electrical	O
&	O
Computer	O
Engineering	O
for	O
Electrical	O
Design	O
Laboratory	O
(ECEN	O
403/404).	O
Guiding	O
undergrad	O
students	O
on	O
projects	O
in	O
the	O
areas	O
of	O
Image	O
Processing,	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
and	O
Microelectronics	O
Nvidia	O
Corporation	O
.	O

◦	O
Keypoint	O
detection:	O
I	O
proposed	O
a	O
simple	O
but	O
eﬃcient	O
algorithm	O
for	O
detecting	O
keypoints.	O
◦	O
Machine	O
learning	O
(ML)	O
production:	O
In	O
order	O
to	O
learn	O
how	O
to	O
go	O
from	O
a	O
ML	O
experiment	O
to	O
a	O
shipped	O
product,	O
I	O
practiced	O
some	O
relevant	O
tools:	O
Android	B-TECH_SKILL
Studio	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
TensorFlow	B-TECH_SKILL
Lite	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

Work	O
experience	O
Scientific	B-ORG
research	I-ORG
project	I-ORG
2020	I-ORG
,	O
Leader	B-POSITION
Jun	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Dec	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Product:	O
Limb	O
rehabilitation	O
equipment.	O
-	O
Research,	O
survey	O
and	O
form	O
development	O
directions	O
for	O
the	O
project.	O
-	O
Implement	O
a	O
SVM	B-TECH_SKILL
model	O
and	O
program	O
for	O
the	O
project.	O
-	O
Assign	O
tasks	O
to	O
members.	O
Result:	O
Awarded	O
the	O
second	O
prize	O
nationwide.	O
Supporting	O
Dak	B-ORG
Lak	I-ORG
science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
technology	I-ORG
team	I-ORG
,	O
Adviser	B-POSITION
Dec	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Apr	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Product:	O
Student	O
monitoring	O
and	O
management	O
system.	O
-	O
Support	O
the	O
product	O
design	O
and	O
programming.	O
-	O
Reinforce	O
the	O
knowledge	O
of	O
Facial	O
Recognition	O
for	O
the	O
team.	O
Result:	O
The	O
Dak	O
Lak	O
team	O
won	O
the	O
first	O
prize	O
nationwide.	O
.	O

Undegraduate,	O
2017–Now	B-TIME
Wichita	B-ORG
State	I-ORG
University,	I-ORG
Wichita,	I-ORG
Kansas.	I-ORG
Junior	I-ORG
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
Major	O
program	O
with	O
Math	O
Minor.	O
.	O

Experience	O
10/2018-	B-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Bizdirect	B-ORG
Asia	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
,	O
HCM	O
City,	O
Data	B-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
.	O

Education	O
BACHALOR	B-DEGREE
DEGREE	I-DEGREE
OF	O
COMMUNICATION	B-MAJOR
SYSTEM	I-MAJOR
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
VNUHCM	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
OF	I-ORG
TECHNOLOGY	I-ORG
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.0/4	I-SCORE
(7.24)	O
.	O

GPA:	B-SCORE
3.90	I-SCORE
⚫	O
Participated	O
in	O
Zalo	O
AI	O
challenge	O
2019	O
as	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
C&E	O
Team.	O
⚫	O
Co-author	O
in	O
the	O
paper	O
"Ensemble	O
Learning	O
For	O
Diabetic	O
Retinopathy"	O
submitted	O
to	O
SSICT-2021	O
(SC203	O
and	O
WR227	O
courses'	O
work).	O
.	O

W	O
O	O
R	O
K	O
E	O
X	O
P	O
E	O
R	O
I	O
E	O
N	O
C	O
E	O
Financial	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
Solutions	I-ORG
-	O
Data	B-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
O	B-TIME
C	I-TIME
T	I-TIME
O	I-TIME
B	I-TIME
E	I-TIME
R	I-TIME
2	I-TIME
0	I-TIME
2	I-TIME
1	I-TIME
T	I-TIME
O	I-TIME
P	I-TIME
R	I-TIME
E	I-TIME
S	I-TIME
E	I-TIME
N	I-TIME
T	I-TIME
Stock	O
Price	O
Manipulation	O
Detection:	O
https://github.com/hieule88/fssstock	O
Researched	O
on	O
stock	O
market	O
domain.	O
Processed	O
data	O
and	O
applied	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
models	O
for	O
panel	O
data.	O
Deployed	O
models	O
using	O
Django	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Celery	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Experience	O
•	O
One	B-ORG
Mount	I-ORG
Hanoi,	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
J	B-POSITION
unior	I-POSITION
Data	I-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
Oct.	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
◦	O
Automated	O
Valuation	O
Model:	O
∗	O
Cleaned	O
and	O
explored	O
data.	O
∗	O
Applied	O
mathematics	O
and	O
statistics	O
to	O
build	O
valuation	O
methods.	O
∗	O
Built	O
and	O
experimented	O
model.	O
∗	O
Visualized	O
and	O
monitored	O
metrics	O
using	O
BI	O
tools	O
(Superset).	O
◦	O
Named	B-TECH_SKILL
Entity	I-TECH_SKILL
Recognition	I-TECH_SKILL
Model	O
for	O
real	O
estate	O
text:	O
Built	O
and	O
fine-tuned	O
model	O
based	O
on	O
SOTA	O
methods.	O
◦	O
Text-matching	O
algorithm:	O
Word	O
vectorization	O
using	O
TF-IDF	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
text-compare	O
using	O
cosine	O
similarity.	O
•	O
Viettel	B-ORG
Digital	I-ORG
Talent	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
Hanoi,	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
Data	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
Intern	B-POSITION
Apr.	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Jul.	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
◦	O
Early	O
prediction	O
of	O
sepsis	O
from	O
clinical	O
data:	O
∗	O
Explored	O
and	O
analyzed	O
data.	O
∗	O
Implemented	O
early	O
predicting	O
sepsis	O
model	O
using	O
machine	O
learning.	O
•	O
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
Hanoi,	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
Software	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Nov.	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Jan.	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
◦	O
Java:	O
Wrote	O
unit	O
and	O
integration	O
test	O
scripts.	O
.	O

.	O

EDUCATION	O
DePauw	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Greencastle	I-ORG
,	O
IN	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Arts	B-MAJOR
Class	O
of	O
2024	B-TIME
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Mathematics	I-MAJOR
Programs:	O
Information	B-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Associate	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
ITAP	I-ORG
Associate	O
Fall	B-TIME
2020-Present	I-TIME
●	O
Developed	O
and	O
learned	O
new	O
skills	O
in	O
various	O
areas	O
of	O
technology,	O
including	O
photoshop,	O
website	O
creation,	O
programming	O
in	O
Python,	O
and	O
data	O
visualization	O
by	O
using	O
Tableau	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

	O
SKILLS	O
Language:	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
Areas	O
of	O
Expertise:	O
NLP,	B-TECH_SKILL
Backend	O
engineer	O
Programing	O
Language:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Javascript	B-TECH_SKILL
Database	O
Language:	O
Mysql	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

SKILLS	O
AND	O
TECHNIQUES	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
for	O
AI/Deep	O
Learning:	O
Can	O
use	O
Numpy	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pandas	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Matplotlib	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
sci-kit	B-TECH_SKILL
learn	I-TECH_SKILL
for	O
Data	O
Visualization.	O
Technique	O
about	O
preprocessing:	O
Processing	O
Missing	O
Data,	O
Imbalanced	O
Data.	O
Have	O
fundamental	O
knowledge	O
about:	O
Supervised	O
Learning	O
and	O
Unsupervived	O
Learning.	O
Have	O
fundamental	O
knowledge	O
Deep	O
Learning:	O
Image	B-TECH_SKILL
Processing	I-TECH_SKILL
for	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Vision	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Natural	B-TECH_SKILL
Language	I-TECH_SKILL
Processing	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
can	O
use	O
basis	O
framework:	O
Keras	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Work	O
experience	O
Smart	O
City	O
07/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
Nova	B-ORG
Intechs	I-ORG
Building	O
models	O
for	O
smart	O
cities,	O
some	O
applications	O
are	O
detect:	O
Detect	O
Personal	O
Protective	O
Equipment	O
at	O
work	O
space,	O
car	O
crash	O
accident,	O
human	O
mask,...	O
For	O
applying	O
multi-functions	O
models	O
in	O
system,	O
we	O
design	O
multi-task	O
model	O
based	O
on	O
Hydranet	O
architecture.	O
AMR	O
03/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
07/2021	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
As	O
project	O
name,	O
AMR	O
-	O
Autonomous	O
Mobile	O
Robot,	O
the	O
goal	O
in	O
this	O
phase	O
is	O
build	O
a	O
autonomous	O
move	O
package	O
inside	O
factories.	O
In	O
this	O
project,	O
my	O
responsibility	O
is	O
build	O
LIDAR	O
to	O
build	O
map,	O
localization,	O
detect	O
human,	O
objects.	O
VIP2020	O
12/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
03/2021	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
Project	O
target	O
is	O
a	O
model	O
can	O
detect	O
vehicles	O
and	O
their	O
types	O
on	O
roads	O
in	O
Japan,	O
the	O
speed	O
of	O
the	O
vehicle	O
and	O
also	O
tracking	O
vehicles	O
throgh	O
camera.	O
My	O
role	O
is	O
collect	O
data	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
huge	O
dataset	O
and	O
tuning	O
model	O
for	O
best	O
accuracy,	O
for	O
every	O
condition	O
of	O
weather	O
like	O
sunny,	O
snow,	O
night,	O
rain,...	O
3DLabelTool	O
10/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
12/2020	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
The	O
goal	O
of	O
this	O
project	O
is	O
build	O
an	O
web	O
application	O
tool	O
for	O
annotation	O
objects	O
in	O
3d	O
space.	O
In	O
this	O
project,	O
we	O
build	O
a	O
web	O
app	O
with	O
Flask	O
and	O
Python	O
on	O
server,	O
an	O
could	O
process	O
hundreds	O
of	O
people	O
work	O
at	O
the	O
same	O
time.	O
Tool	O
can	O
view,	O
zoom,	O
draw	O
or	O
do	O
anything	O
in	O
space	O
show	O
up	O
on	O
web	O
and	O
save	O
the	O
information	O
back	O
to	O
server.	O
FURUNO	O
07/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
10/2020	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
FURUNO	O
target	O
is	O
2	O
points.	O
First,	O
they	O
want	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
full	O
data	O
set	O
with	O
any	O
conditions	O
possible:	O
sunny,	O
rain,	O
foggy,	O
snow,	O
etc,	O
in	O
every	O
time	O
in	O
the	O
day.	O
My	O
work	O
in	O
this	O
project	O
is	O
analysis	O
data,	O
and	O
have	O
the	O
result	O
about	O
the	O
weather,	O
image	O
quality,	O
etc	O
aﬀect	O
to	O
the	O
accuracy	O
of	O
model.	O
Also,	O
I	O
deﬁne	O
the	O
model	O
architect	O
to	O
detect	O
object	O
in	O
the	O
ocean.	O
Raster	O
to	O
Vector	O
05/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
07/2020	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
Customer	O
want	O
an	O
AI	O
system	O
can	O
scan	O
the	O
hand-draw	O
technical	O
drawings	O
and	O
transfer	O
them	O
to	O
CAD.	O
My	O
work	O
is	O
build	O
a	O
model	O
to	O
detect	O
arrow,	O
symbols	O
to	O
redraw	O
in	O
CAD.	O
The	O
hard	O
thing	O
here	O
is	O
deal	O
with	O
very	O
less	O
data,	O
and	O
very	O
imbalance	O
between	O
symbols.	O
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
FREELANCE	O
WORK	O
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
Wedding	B-ORG
Waiter	I-ORG
Skills	O
gained:	O
Be	O
a	O
better	O
listener	O
and	O
more	O
careful.	O
WORK	O
IN	O
UNIVERSITY	O
2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
Undergraduate/	O
Member	O
in	O
a	O
group	O
Main	O
responsibilities:-	O
Complete	O
the	O
group	O
assignments	O
or	O
projects	O
related	O
to	O
my	O
major	O
assigned	O
by	O
lecturers.	O
Skills	O
gained:-	O
Practice	O
teamwork	B-SOFT_SKILL
skills.	O
-	O
Acquire	O
more	O
about	O
these	O
topics	O
.	O

Education	O
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Nong	B-ORG
Lam	I-ORG
University.	I-ORG
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
(Honors	O
Program)	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.99/10	I-SCORE
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science,	I-ORG
VNU-HCM	I-ORG
September	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
.	O

EDUCATION	O
.............................................................................................................................................	O
MASTER	B-DEGREE
DEGREE	I-DEGREE
IN	O
INFORMATION	B-MAJOR
TECHNOLOGY	I-MAJOR
-	I-MAJOR
DATA	I-MAJOR
SCIENCE	I-MAJOR
MAJOR	O
|	O
JUL	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
JUL	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Queensland	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
(QUT)	I-ORG
Cumulative	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
7.0/7.0	I-SCORE
Awards:	O
International	O
Merit	O
Scholarship,	O
Dean's	O
List	O
for	O
Excellent	O
Academic	O
Performance	O
Research	O
project:	O
Computer	O
vision-based	O
detection	O
of	O
neurons	O
in	O
2D	O
slices	O
of	O
mouse	O
brain	O
images	O
obtained	O
from	O
tissue	O
clearing	O
and	O
Light-Sheet	O
Fluoresence	O
Microscopy.	O
Activities:	O
Vice	B-POSITION
President	I-POSITION
of	O
QUT	O
Business	O
Analytics	O
and	O
Data	O
Science	O
club	O
QUT	O
Connector	O
-	O
volunteering	O
to	O
help	O
first-year	O
students	O
kick	O
off	O
university	O
College	O
of	O
Excellence	O
member	O
BACHELOR	B-DEGREE
DEGREE	I-DEGREE
IN	O
INTERNATIONAL	B-MAJOR
BUSINESS	I-MAJOR
ECONOMICS	I-MAJOR
|	O
AUG	B-TIME
2013	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
AUG	I-TIME
2017	I-TIME
Foreign	B-ORG
Trade	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Cumulative	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.34/4	I-SCORE
Achievements:	O
A	O
score	O
for	O
graduation	O
thesis,	O
Scholarship	O
for	O
Excellent	O
Academic	O
Performance	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
student	O
VNUHCM-University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
•	O
Participating	O
in	O
MICCAI	O
2022	O
challenges	O
and	O
workshops.	O
•	O
Participated	O
in	O
Shopee	O
Code	O
League	O
2022.	O
•	O
Participated	O
in	O
SHREC	O
2022.	O
•	O
Participated	O
in	O
MediaEval	O
2021.	O
•	O
Participated	O
in	O
Thach	O
Thuc	O
2020.	O
.	O

●	O
Introduced	O
the	O
product’s	O
core	O
feature	O
by	O
implementing	O
the	O
programming	O
testing	O
system.	O
.	O

EXPERIMENTS	O
Researcher	B-POSITION
at	O
UET-AIlab	B-ORG
VNU	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
�	O
2020	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
Viettel	B-ORG
Digital	I-ORG
Talent	I-ORG
Program	O
2021	O
�	O
Apr	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
.	O

EDUCATION	O
AND	O
TRAINING	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
Talented	O
BSc	B-DEGREE
in	O
Physics	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Electronics	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
GPA	B-SCORE
3.3	I-SCORE
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
.	O

Mathematics:	O
Linear	O
Algebra,	O
Probability	O
and	O
Statistic,	O
Calculus	O
(vector,	O
multivariable),	O
Discrete	O
Math.	O
Machine	O
Learning:	O
Firmly	O
understand	O
Deep	O
learning	O
terminologies,	O
networks	O
(	O
CNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
RNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
LSTM	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
BERT	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
GANs	B-TECH_SKILL
...)	O
and	O
understand	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
terminologies:	O
VAR	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
REM	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
FEM	B-TECH_SKILL
,...	O
.	O

SKILLS	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
-	O
625	O
TOEIC	B-SOFT_SKILL
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
SQL	I-TECH_SKILL
Office	B-SOFT_SKILL
Self-study	O
Research	O
.	O

EMPLOYMENT	O
HISTORY	O
Intern	B-POSITION
Software	I-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
at	O
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
,	O
Hanoi	O
September	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
—	I-TIME
July	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	O
Write	O
code	O
&	O
documentation	O
for	O
UI	O
libraries	O
to	O
used	O
in	O
payment	O
applications	O
-	O
Participate	O
in	O
develop	O
simultaneously	O
two	O
payment	O
applications	O
for	O
two	O
of	O
Vietnam's	O
biggest	O
bank	O
-	O
Majority	O
of	O
time	O
code	O
in	O
Kotlin,	O
in	O
addition	O
also	O
experiences	O
with	O
HTML/CSS	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
when	O
writing	O
development	O
guide	O
-	O
Worked	O
in	O
two	O
different	O
projects,	O
each	O
with	O
distinct	O
requirements	O
Student	B-POSITION
Ambassador	I-POSITION
at	O
School	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Computing	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Leeds	I-ORG
,	O
Leeds	O
October	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
—	I-TIME
June	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	O
Worked	O
during	O
university	O
open	O
days	O
and	O
applicant	O
days	O
for	O
the	O
school	O
-	O
Assisted	O
with	O
lab	O
activities	O
and	O
university	O
tour	O
-	O
Talked	O
to	O
student	O
and	O
parents	O
about	O
the	O
university,	O
course	O
and	O
answer	O
any	O
enquiries	O
.	O

ASSIGNMENTS	O
Online	O
Shopping	O
Website	O
Technologies:	O
HTML	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
CSS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Javascript	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
PHP	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
MySQL	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Design	O
and	O
build	O
a	O
layout	O
using	O
HTML	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
CSS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
and	O
Javascript	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

S	O
K	O
I	O
L	O
L	O
S	O
S	O
U	O
M	O
M	O
A	O
R	O
Y	O
Data	O
Structure,	O
Object	B-TECH_SKILL
Oriented	I-TECH_SKILL
Programming	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Vision	I-TECH_SKILL
Familiar	O
with	O
programming	O
languages	O
such	O
as:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
Familiar	O
with	O
various	O
tools	O
such	O
as:	O
MS	B-TECH_SKILL
Visual	I-TECH_SKILL
Studio	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
MS	B-TECH_SKILL
Visual	I-TECH_SKILL
Studio	I-TECH_SKILL
Code	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Anaconda	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science,	I-ORG
VNUHCM	I-ORG
(	O
2018	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
)	O
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.37/10.0	I-SCORE
.	O

.	O

SKILLS	O
Programming	O
Language	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
Framework	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
Other	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Skills	O
Python	O
4+	O
yrs.	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
3+	O
yrs.	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
4+	O
yrs.	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
3+	O
yrs.	O
Data	O
analysis	O
3+	O
yrs.	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
TOEIC	O
635/990	O
.	O

RESEARCH	O
EXPERIENCE	O
UET-AI	B-ORG
lab	I-ORG
September	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Researcher	I-POSITION
Hanoi,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
•	O
Research	O
under	O
the	O
lead	O
of	O
Dr.	O
Tran	O
Quoc	O
Long.	O
•	O
Image	B-TECH_SKILL
Enhancement	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Image	B-TECH_SKILL
Quality	I-TECH_SKILL
Assessment	I-TECH_SKILL
:	O
∗	O
Implement	O
state-of-the-art	O
models	O
and	O
evaluate	O
on	O
benchmark	O
datasets.	O
Develop	O
differentiable	O
function	O
to	O
extract	O
some	O
special	O
feature	O
image.	O
•	O
Chatbot:	O
∗	O
Research	O
about	O
Natural	B-TECH_SKILL
Language	I-TECH_SKILL
Understanding	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Dialogue	B-TECH_SKILL
System	I-TECH_SKILL
Tracking	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Brisbane,	B-LOC
Australia	I-LOC
The	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Queensland	I-ORG
Feb	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Dec	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
•	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Engineering	I-DEGREE
(Honors)	O
–	O
Major:	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
•	O
Current	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
6.25/7	I-SCORE
•	O
Relevant	O
courses:	O
Computer	O
System	O
Principles	O
&	O
Programming,	O
Human-Computer	O
Interaction,	O
Artificial	O
Intelligent,	O
Advanced	O
Data	O
Structures	O
&	O
Algorithms,	O
Design	O
Computing	O
Studio,	O
Engineering	O
Problem	O
Solving,	O
Machine	O
Learning,	O
Compiler	O
and	O
Interpreter,	O
Pattern	O
Recognition	O
and	O
Analysis	O
•	O
Transferred	O
from	O
Ho	O
Chi	O
Minh	O
City	O
University	O
of	O
Technology	O
Ho	O
Chi	O
Minh	O
City,	O
Vietnam	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Aug	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Dec	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
•	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
Program	O
–	O
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.28/10	I-SCORE
•	O
Relevant	O
courses:	O
Discrete	O
Mathematics,	O
Object	O
Oriented	O
Programming,	O
Algorithms	O
&	O
Data	O
Structures,	O
Operating	O
System,	O
Database	O
Systems,	O
Math	O
Modeling,	O
Probability	O
&	O
Statistics	O
Ho	O
Chi	O
Minh	O
City,	O
Vietnam	O
VNU-HCM	B-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
The	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
Aug	B-TIME
2014	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2017	I-TIME
•	O
Math	B-MAJOR
specialized	O
class	O
.	O

SKILLS	O
	O
Knowledge	O
of	O
Linear	O
Algebra,	O
Probability	O
	O
Work	O
with	O
many	O
framework	O
like	O
and	O
Statistic	O
Basic.	O
Tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Darknet	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

SOFT	O
SKILLS	O
Presentation	B-SOFT_SKILL
Skills	O
Problem	B-SOFT_SKILL
Solving	I-SOFT_SKILL
T	O
eam	B-SOFT_SKILL
Leaderships	I-SOFT_SKILL
Time	I-SOFT_SKILL
Management	I-SOFT_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Rutgers	B-ORG
University,	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
Brunswick,	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
Jersey:	I-ORG
●	O
M.S	B-DEGREE
in	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
(	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.	I-SCORE
83	I-SCORE
)	O
Expected	O
05/2023	B-TIME
●	O
B.S	B-DEGREE
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
(Magna	O
Cum	O
Laude)	O
05/2021	O
Dean	O
list	O
(Fall	O
2019	O
-	O
Spring	O
2021)	O
.	O

KINH	O
NGHIỆM	O
VNG	B-ORG
,	O
Software	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
5/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
8/2021	I-TIME
●	O
Thiết	O
kế	O
và	O
hiện	O
thực	O
UI,	O
logic	O
cho	O
game	O
chiến	O
lược	O
thời	O
gian	O
thực,	O
sử	O
dụng	O
JavaScript	B-TECH_SKILL
và	O
Cocos2d	B-TECH_SKILL
framework.	O
●	O
Giải	O
quyết	O
bài	O
toán	O
đồng	O
bộ	O
giữa	O
client-server	O
cho	O
chế	O
độ	O
PVP	O
trong	O
game,	O
sử	O
dụng	O
ngôn	O
ngữ	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

	O
Knowleage	O
of	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
Algorithm.	O
	O
Programing	O
language:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C/C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
	O
Able	O
to	O
learn	O
and	O
use	O
Deep	O
learning	O
SOTA	O
Matlab	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
COMPUTER	B-ORG
VISION	I-ORG
COMPANY	I-ORG
(STEALTH	O
MODE)	O
(	O
Apr.	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
now	I-TIME
)	O
AI	B-POSITION
ENGINEER	I-POSITION
INTERN	I-POSITION
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
•	O
Optimize	O
current	O
AI	O
services	O
•	O
Build	O
and	O
train	O
models	O
•	O
Deploy	O
to	O
productions	O
Projects:	O
•	O
Text	O
Recognition	O
on	O
Identity	O
Cards	O
•	O
Facial	O
Security	O
System	O
Skills	O
gained:	O
•	O
DL	O
models	O
optimization	B-TECH_SKILL
•	O
Efficiently	O
programming	O
ROBOTICS	B-ORG
AND	I-ORG
VISION	I-ORG
LAB	I-ORG
(	O
Oct.	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
now	I-TIME
)	O
AI	B-POSITION
DEVELOPER	I-POSITION
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
•	O
Research	O
and	O
optimize	O
a	O
developed	O
project	O
•	O
Simulate	O
mobile	O
robot	O
in	O
MATLAB	B-TECH_SKILL
Projects:	O
•	O
(on-going)	O
Applying	O
AI	O
and	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Vision	I-TECH_SKILL
in	O
Mobile	O
Robot	O
navigation.	O
Source	O
code:	O
https://github.com/anhdang000/mobile_robot_RL	O
Skills	O
gained:	O
•	O
Acquisition	O
of	O
knowledge	O
and	O
experience	O
in	O
Reinforcement	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
•	O
Self-learning	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
June	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
September	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
BTEC	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
Major:	O
Website	B-MAJOR
develop	I-MAJOR
June	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Devember	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Online	O
course	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
Django	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
Link:	O
-	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
:	O
https://www.udemy.com/course/complete-python-developer-	O
://www.udemy.com/course/django-course/	O
zero-to-mastery/https	O
-	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
:	O
https://codelearn.io/learning/basic-sql-for-developer	O
January	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
Odoo	B-ORG
Python	B-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
and	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
Major	I-POSITION
:	O
Odoo	B-TECH_SKILL
Python	I-TECH_SKILL
developer	O
Having	O
over	O
1	O
years	O
of	O
experience	O
in	O
building	O
and	O
designing	O
software	O
using	O
Odoo	B-TECH_SKILL
framework	O
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Sr.	O
DATA	B-POSITION
SCIENTIST	I-POSITION
,	O
Actuate	B-ORG
AI,	I-ORG
New	I-ORG
York	I-ORG
City,	I-ORG
NY	I-ORG
November	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
January	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
●	O
Designed/deployed	O
an	O
incremental	O
learning	O
pipeline	O
to	O
autonomate	O
collect/process	O
data	O
and	O
train/test/deploy	O
new	O
models	O
in	O
development,	O
handling	O
100M+	O
images	O
per	O
day,	O
data	O
collected	O
based	O
on	O
detection	O
distribution	O
across	O
camera	O
sites,	O
verified	O
daily	O
and	O
sampled	O
to	O
new	O
train/test	O
database.	O
The	O
distributed	O
auto-train	O
starts	O
weekly	O
with	O
collected/processed	O
data	O
from	O
inference,	O
model	O
was	O
auto-compiled	O
for	O
AWS	O
Inferentia	O
chips,	O
then	O
model	O
was	O
tested	O
on	O
in-house	O
database	O
and	O
deployed	O
for	O
A/B	O
testing	O
with	O
custom	O
metrics.	O
Compiling	O
saves	O
75-80%	O
cost	O
compared	O
to	O
T4	O
GPU	O
inference,	O
the	O
pipeline	O
reduced	O
up	O
to	O
80%	O
workload	O
of	O
data	O
science	O
team,	O
leaving	O
only	O
human	O
verification	O
step,	O
impacting	O
all	O
ML	O
products,	O
custom	O
metrics	O
are	O
effective	O
to	O
categorize	O
performance	O
on	O
different	O
environments,	O
settings.	O
After	O
verification,	O
the	O
model	O
was	O
auto-deployed	O
to	O
as	O
an	O
AWS	O
Endpoint	O
and	O
the	O
loop	O
started	O
again.	O
●	O
Built/customized	O
machine	O
learning	O
models	O
(	O
YOLO	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SSD	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
EfficientDet	B-TECH_SKILL
)	O
for	O
weapon-detection/tracking	O
in	O
real-time.	O
Products	O
are	O
able	O
to	O
detect	O
threats	O
(weapons,	O
behavior)	O
with	O
high	O
accuracy	O
(99.95%+)	O
and	O
True	O
Positive,	O
and	O
low	O
False	O
Positive	O
(0-3/camera/month).	O
Several	O
models	O
were	O
deployed	O
to	O
almost	O
25000+	O
cameras	O
in	O
1000+	O
schools	O
and	O
facilities.	O
Using	O
Darknet	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
inference	O
in	O
AWS	B-TECH_SKILL
Inferentia	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
tkDNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
OpenCV	B-TECH_SKILL
-dnn.	O
Also	O
deployed	O
on	O
iOS	O
and	O
Android.	O
●	O
Researched	O
and	O
integrated	O
features	O
to	O
other	O
CV	O
algorithms	O
(segmentation,	O
detection,	O
tracking)	O
for	O
specific	O
tasks	O
(threat,	O
traffic,	O
security).	O
Implemented	O
test-time	O
augmentation,	O
OpenPifPaf	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
YOLACT++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
boosted	O
recall	O
while	O
maintaining	O
precision.	O
Integrated	O
multi-channel	O
training	O
to	O
improve	O
performance	O
of	O
detection	O
on	O
static	O
CCTV.	O
●	O
Optimized	O
structure	O
of	O
backend	O
logic	O
to	O
reduce	O
cost	O
by	O
30%	O
while	O
boosting	O
recall	O
and	O
precision.	O
The	O
process:	O
Detect	O
motion,	O
increase	O
frame	O
sampling	O
rate,	O
preprocess	O
input,	O
send	O
input	O
to	O
detection	O
layers,	O
get	O
result	O
&	O
compress	O
frames,	O
send	O
information	O
to	O
database,	O
update	O
logs	O
to	O
analytics	O
platforms.	O
DATA	B-POSITION
SCIENTIST	I-POSITION
,	O
Veda	B-ORG
Grace	I-ORG
Dermatology,	I-ORG
Chicago,	I-ORG
IL	I-ORG
July	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
January	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
●	O
Implemented	O
image	O
processing	O
features	O
and	O
built	O
classification	O
models	O
based	O
on	O
ResNet	B-TECH_SKILL
to	O
analyze	O
skin	O
images,	O
recognize	O
conditions	O
and	O
provide	O
recommendations	O
for	O
patients.	O
Deployed	O
in	O
AWS	B-TECH_SKILL
Lambda	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Email:	O
quantum.2681@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
VinBrain	B-ORG
HCMC	I-ORG
,	O
Vietnam	B-LOC
Applied	B-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Apr.	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug.	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
●	O
Improving	O
the	O
object	O
detection	O
model	O
mAP@0.5	O
score	O
over	O
two	O
times	O
from	O
a	O
pretrained	O
model	O
when	O
tested	O
on	O
a	O
custom	O
version	O
of	O
the	O
Open	O
Images	O
v6	O
dataset.	O
LSIR,	B-ORG
École	I-ORG
Polytechnique	I-ORG
Fédérale	I-ORG
de	I-ORG
Lausanne	I-ORG
Lausanne,	B-LOC
Switzerland	I-LOC
(Remote	O
from	O
Vietnam	O
due	O
to	O
COVID-19)	O
Research	B-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
May	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Dec.	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
●	O
Worked	O
on	O
a	O
Subtree-Reuse-based	O
SQL	O
Query	O
Optimizer	O
using	O
Graph	B-TECH_SKILL
Neural	I-TECH_SKILL
Network	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Box	O
Embeddings.	O
●	O
Performed	O
experiments	O
on	O
the	O
Attribute	O
Discovery	O
dataset	O
to	O
verify	O
the	O
plausibility	O
of	O
a	O
new	O
Multimodal	O
Feature	O
Fusion	O
method	O
using	O
Graph	B-TECH_SKILL
Neural	I-TECH_SKILL
Network	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
achieving	O
a	O
test	O
accuracy	O
of	O
96.86%	O
on	O
this	O
dataset.	O
Faculty	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology,	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science,	I-ORG
VNU-HCM	I-ORG
HCMC	I-ORG
,	O
Vietnam	O
Research	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
Sep.	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug.	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
●	O
Discovered	O
the	O
correlation	O
between	O
forking	O
patterns	O
and	O
software	O
health	O
and	O
risks	O
in	O
software	O
repositories.	O
●	O
Performed	O
inference	O
in	O
the	O
Software	O
Heritage	O
Dataset	O
to	O
extract	O
forking	O
patterns	O
between	O
50,000	O
repositories	O
using	O
PostgreSQL	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Neo4J.	O
Big-O	B-ORG
Coding	I-ORG
HCMC,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
Teaching	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
,	O
Problem	B-POSITION
Setter	I-POSITION
,	O
Front-end	B-POSITION
Web	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
Jul.	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Dec.	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
●	O
Explained	O
Algorithms	O
and	O
Data	O
Structures	O
concepts	O
to	O
students	O
at	O
Big-O	B-ORG
Coding	I-ORG
weekly	O
and	O
prepared	O
more	O
than	O
20	O
programming	O
problems.	O
●	O
Built	O
version	O
1	O
of	O
the	O
Front-end	O
Web	O
Application	O
for	O
Big-O	B-ORG
Coding	I-ORG
’s	O
website:	O
http://bigocoder.com	O
to	O
host	O
programming	O
problems	O
and	O
programming	O
contests	O
for	O
up	O
to	O
1,900	O
users	O
using	O
React	B-TECH_SKILL
JS	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

SKILLS	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
N	O
atural	B-TECH_SKILL
Language	I-TECH_SKILL
Processing	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Mathematics,	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

SKILLS	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
Deep	O
Learning	O
Python	O
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
OpenCV	I-TECH_SKILL
Pytorch	I-TECH_SKILL
Tensorﬂow	I-TECH_SKILL
NLP	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Quoc-Trinh	B-NAME
Tran	I-NAME
�	O
(+84)	B-PHONE
793587822	I-PHONE
�	O
tranquoctrinh.ai@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
Curriculum	O
Vitae	O
�	O
github.com/tranquoctrinh	O
.	O

Minh	B-NAME
Pham	I-NAME
.	O

EDUCATION	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Economics	I-ORG
HCMC	I-ORG
International	B-MAJOR
Business	I-MAJOR
(	O
2016-2020	B-TIME
)	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.55	I-SCORE
English	O
IELTS	O
7.5	O
Advanced	O
level	O
at	O
four	O
skills	O
Machine	O
learning	O
course	O
Stanford	O
University	O
(Coursera)	O
Machine	O
learning	O
Basics	O
Course	O
Microsoft	O
Office	O
IC3	O
Digital	O
Literacy	O
Certification	O
Data	O
Analysis	O
&	O
Planning	O
ERP	O
Certificate	O
Enterprise	O
Resource	O
Planning	O
.	O

•	O
Project	O
Audio	O
book	O
–	O
Science	O
project	O
in	O
collaboration	O
with	O
VOV	O
radio	O
station.	O
–	O
Applied	O
text	O
to	O
speech	O
technology	O
to	O
produce	O
audio	O
books.	O
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
11/2020	B-TIME
—	I-TIME
09/2021	I-TIME
Sun	B-ORG
Asterisk	I-ORG
VN	I-ORG
•	O
License	O
plate	O
recognition	O
-	O
PoC	O
�	O
–	O
Researched	O
deep	O
learning	O
methods	O
for	O
Vietnamese	O
license	O
plates	O
detection	O
and	O
recognition.	O
–	O
Deployed	O
model	O
on	O
NVIDIA	O
Jetson	O
Nano.	O
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
06/2020	B-TIME
—	I-TIME
08/2020	I-TIME
Skymap	B-ORG
Global	I-ORG
VN	I-ORG
•	O
Worked	O
with	O
QGIS	O
to	O
interact	O
with	O
satellite	O
images.	O
•	O
Developed	O
deep	O
learning	O
model	O
to	O
automatically	O
extract	O
building	O
footprint	O
from	O
satellite	O
images.	O
.	O

Education	O
HCMC	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
and	O
Major:	O
Mechatronics	B-MAJOR
Aug	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Apr	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Education,	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.42/10	I-SCORE
Rank	O
very	O
good	O
students	O
in	O
6	O
terms.	O
Achieve	O
academic	O
scholarships	O
2020,	O
2021.	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Myongji	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Korea	O
March	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
February	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
M.Sc.	B-DEGREE
in	O
Electronics	O
Engineering,	O
Major	O
in	O
Machine	B-MAJOR
Learning	I-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Signal	I-MAJOR
Processing	I-MAJOR
Overall	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
4.19/4.5	I-SCORE
Belgorod	B-ORG
National	I-ORG
Research	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Russia	O
November	B-TIME
2010	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
May	I-TIME
2015	I-TIME
B.Sc.	B-DEGREE
in	O
Physics	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
Overall	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
4.5/5	I-SCORE
.	O

Building	O
appropriate	O
metrics,	O
based	O
on	O
Optimal	B-TECH_SKILL
Transport	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
statistics,	O
to	O
measure	O
Domain	B-TECH_SKILL
Shift	I-TECH_SKILL
/	O
Concept	B-TECH_SKILL
Shift	I-TECH_SKILL
in	O
data.	O
Devising	O
an	O
online	O
learning	O
method	O
to	O
adaptively	O
re-sampling	O
data	O
overtime	O
for	O
model	O
training	O
based	O
on	O
Concept	B-TECH_SKILL
Drift	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
history	O
results	O
01/2021-	B-TIME
Modelling	B-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
at	O
Tien	B-ORG
Phong	I-ORG
Bank,	I-ORG
TPBank	I-ORG
06/2021	B-TIME
Fitting	O
appropriate	O
distribution	O
for	O
Probability	O
of	O
Default	O
for	O
different	O
segments,	O
using	O
Estimation	O
Technique.	O
Building	O
Regression	O
models	O
to	O
predict	O
forward-looking	O
Probability	O
of	O
Default	O
for	O
multiple	O
segments,	O
using	O
Macroeconomics	O
factors	O
overtime.	O
Devising	O
multiple	O
tests	O
.	O

Skills	O
•	O
Programming	O
Languages:	O
JavaScript	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
R	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
HTML	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
CSS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C/C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C#	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
•	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	O
Major:	O
Physics	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
Physics	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
6.9/10	I-SCORE
Oct	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
.	O

LÊ	B-NAME
THANH	I-NAME
PHƯƠNG	I-NAME
.	O

Phạm	B-NAME
Minh	I-NAME
Huy	I-NAME
Kiến	I-NAME
Hưng	I-NAME
–	O
Hà	B-LOC
Đông	I-LOC
–	I-LOC
Hà	I-LOC
Nội	I-LOC
Phone:	O
0988419418	B-PHONE
⚫	O
Email:	O
pmhuy2209@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
MAJOR:	O
COMPUTER	B-MAJOR
SCIENCE	I-MAJOR
UNIVERSITY	B-ORG
OF	I-ORG
SCIENCE	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
VIETNAM	I-ORG
NATIONAL	I-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
AUG	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
GPA:	O
-out	O
of	O
10:	O
8.05	B-SCORE
-	O
out	O
of	O
4:	O
3.5	B-SCORE
SPECIALIZE	O
SUBJECT:	O
MATHEMATICS	B-ORG
NGUYEN	I-ORG
BINH	I-ORG
KHIEM	I-ORG
HIGH	I-ORG
SCHOOL	I-ORG
FOR	I-ORG
THE	I-ORG
GIFTED	I-ORG
AUG	B-TIME
2014	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
MAY	I-TIME
2017	I-TIME
Graduated	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
HCMC	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Education,	I-ORG
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City,	I-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
Sep-17	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
Sep-21	I-TIME
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science	I-DEGREE
in	O
Information	B-MAJOR
Technology	I-MAJOR
.	O

.	O

S	O
K	O
I	O
L	O
L	O
S	O
Programming	O
language:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
JavaScript	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Node.js	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C#	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

Computer	B-POSITION
Vision	I-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
.	O

Experience	O
Digital	O
Graduate	O
at	O
FWD	B-POSITION
Insurance	I-POSITION
8/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
(full-time)	O
As	O
a	O
digital	O
graduate,	O
I	O
will	O
rotate	O
three	O
different	O
departments	O
to	O
grasp	O
the	O
insurance	O
industry's	O
knowledge	O
and	O
apply	O
my	O
digital	O
knowledge	O
to	O
enhance	O
the	O
traditional	O
processes.	O
1st	O
rotation:	O
Digital	O
and	O
Data	O
(	O
from	B-TIME
8/2021	I-TIME
to	I-TIME
3/2022	I-TIME
)	O
Design	O
eKYC	B-TECH_SKILL
user	O
flow	O
for	O
current	O
sale	O
platform	O
Build	O
AI	O
model	O
for	O
early	O
lapse	O
detection	O
2nd	O
rotation:	O
Product	O
Team	O
(	O
from	B-TIME
3/2022	I-TIME
to	I-TIME
9/2022	I-TIME
)	O
Report	O
product	O
performance	O
Build	O
riders'	O
recommendation	O
system	O
Data	O
Analytics	O
Teaching	B-POSITION
Assistance	I-POSITION
at	O
CoderSchool	O
4/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
(part-time)	O
Tutoring	O
data	O
analytics	O
skills:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

23/1E	B-LOC
To	I-LOC
Ky	I-LOC
Street,	I-LOC
Hoc	I-LOC
Mon	I-LOC
District,	I-LOC
Ho	I-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
0853935961	B-PHONE
hieuminhnguyen95@gm	B-EMAIL
ail.com	I-EMAIL
https://www.linkedin.co	O
m/in/hieu-nguyen-	O
8b13771a4/	O
.	O

.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Front-end	B-POSITION
Web	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
BT	B-ORG
tech	I-ORG
corporation	I-ORG
03/2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
08/2019	I-TIME
,	O
Hanoi,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
Achievements/Tasks	O
Maintain	O
and	O
develop	O
responsive	O
websites.	O
Finish	O
the	O
reusability	O
scripts,	O
Restful	B-TECH_SKILL
API	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
STUDENT	O
Sep	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
VNUHCM	I-ORG
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.66/10	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
UNIVERSITY	B-ORG
OF	I-ORG
TECHNOLOGY	I-ORG
2015-12/2019	B-TIME
This	O
was	O
the	O
period	O
I	O
studied	O
and	O
graduated	O
computer	B-MAJOR
science	I-MAJOR
at	O
the	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology.	I-ORG
.	O

EDUCATION	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
(HCMUS)	I-ORG
Sep	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Sep	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Major	O
:	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Computer	I-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.05/10	I-SCORE
•	O
Coursework:	O
Linear	O
Algebra,	O
Probability	O
and	O
Statistics,	O
Calculus	O
I,	O
II,	O
III,	O
Data	O
Structure	O
and	O
Algorithm,	O
Data	O
Visualization,	O
Artiﬁcial	O
Intelligent,	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
APRIL	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
PRESENT	I-TIME
DATA	B-ORG
SCIENCE	I-ORG
LAB	I-ORG
(HUST)	I-ORG
|	O
Member	B-POSITION
of	O
the	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
group	O
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
-	O
Learn	O
the	O
basics	O
of	O
machine	O
learning	O
and	O
deep	O
learning.	O
-	O
Reading	O
papers,	O
weekly	O
seminar	O
about	O
Continual	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Amsterdam	I-ORG
Highschool	I-ORG
Math	B-MAJOR
Major	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.1/10.0	I-SCORE
Union	B-ORG
College	I-ORG
,	O
Schenectady,	O
New	O
York	O
(Scholars	O
Program)	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
Major,	O
Math	B-MAJOR
&	I-MAJOR
Statistic	I-MAJOR
Minor	I-MAJOR
Major	O
&	O
Minor	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
4.0/4.0	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
September	B-TIME
2016	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
July	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Electrical	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Telecommunication	I-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
CPA:	B-SCORE
3.4/4.0	I-SCORE
Related	O
courses:	O
Calculus,	O
Algebra,	O
Probability	O
and	O
Statistics,	O
Applied	O
Algorithms.	O
.	O

Experience	O
07/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Research	B-POSITION
–	O
Control	B-ORG
and	I-ORG
Automation	I-ORG
Laboratory	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
HCMUT	I-ORG
•	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
(	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
Reinforcement	I-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
)	O
integration	O
in	O
Robotics	O
–	O
Final	O
Thesis	O
•	O
Paper:	O
3D	O
Printing	O
System	O
Using	O
Nonplanar	O
Slicing	O
Technique	O
07/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Engineer	B-POSITION
Interns	I-POSITION
–	O
Think	B-ORG
Alpha	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
•	O
Researcher	O
in	O
Robotics	O
&	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
field	O
•	O
R&D	O
Engineer	O
–	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
&	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
Engineer	O
•	O
Project	O
Engineer	O
–	O
Embedded	O
Engineer	O
08/2021	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
10/2021	I-TIME
Software	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
–	O
Think	B-ORG
Alpha	I-ORG
Company	I-ORG
•	O
Full-stack	B-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
–	O
TechLead	B-POSITION
of	O
Company	O
Website	O
Project	O
•	O
QR	O
code	O
Scanner	O
Project	O
•	O
Peer	O
to	O
Peer	O
Real-time	O
Chatting	O
Application	O
05/2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
06/2019	I-TIME
Participant	B-POSITION
–	O
Design	O
&	O
Control	O
the	O
Model	O
Aircraft	O
Contest	O
of	O
HCMUT	O
•	O
UAV	O
system	O
Designer	O
&	O
Programmer	O
–	O
Team	O
Leader	O
.	O

NGUYEN	B-NAME
HUU	I-NAME
THUAT	I-NAME
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
.	O

	O
WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
MAR	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
MAY	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Gameloft	B-ORG
,	O
Programming	B-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
-	O
Learn	O
deeper	O
knowledge	O
in	O
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Create	O
a	O
personal	O
game	O
DEC	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
APR	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
VCCorp	B-ORG
,	O
Data	B-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
-	O
Implement	O
state-of-the-art	O
models	O
to	O
improve	O
news	O
recommendation	O
system	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
QUEBEC	B-ORG
UNIVERSITY	I-ORG
M.SC	B-DEGREE
IN	O
APPLIED	B-MAJOR
MATHEMATICS	I-MAJOR
AND	I-MAJOR
COMPUTER	I-MAJOR
SCIENCE	I-MAJOR
TOPIC	O
:	O
MACHINE	O
LEARNING	O
AND	O
STATISTICS	O
Sep	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Apr	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
|	O
Trois-Rivieres	O
,Canada	O
AIX-MARSEILLE	B-ORG
UNIVSERSITY	I-ORG
BS	B-DEGREE
IN	O
MATHEMATICS	B-MAJOR
Grad.	O
Jul	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
|	O
Marseille	O
,	O
France	B-ORG
ECOLE	I-ORG
POLYTECHNIQUE	I-ORG
MENG	I-ORG
IN	I-ORG
CIVIL	I-ORG
ENGINEERING	I-ORG
AND	I-ORG
MATERIALS	I-ORG
Interrupted	I-ORG
|	O
Montreal,Qc	B-LOC
.	O

Education	O
2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
now	I-TIME
Master	B-DEGREE
at	O
Vietnamese-German	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
,	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
Major:	O
Computational	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Master	B-MAJOR
at	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Natural	I-ORG
Sciences	I-ORG
,	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
Major:	O
Theoretical	B-MAJOR
Physics	I-MAJOR
2014	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
Bachelor	B-MAJOR
at	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Natural	I-ORG
Sciences	I-ORG
,	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
Major:	O
Theoretical	B-MAJOR
Physics	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.24/10	I-SCORE
.	O

.	O

Sep.	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Student	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City,	I-LOC
VN	I-LOC
•	O
Multimedia	B-ORG
Communications	I-ORG
Laboratory	I-ORG
(MMLab)	I-ORG
•	O
Main	O
research	O
domain:	O
Document	O
Analysis,	O
Medical	O
Image	B-TECH_SKILL
Segmentation	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Traﬃc	O
Surveillance	O
Camera	O
System	O
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.80/10	I-SCORE
.	O

Tư	O
duy	O
học	O
thuật	O
Có	O
nền	O
tảng	O
thuật	O
toán	O
và	O
cấu	O
trúc	O
dữ	O
liệu	O
Phân	O
tích	O
thiết	O
kế	O
hệ	O
thống	O
Tư	O
duy,	O
kiến	O
thức	O
cơ	O
bản	O
Làm	O
việc	O
nhóm	O
Khả	O
năng	O
hòa	O
nhập	O
tốt	O
và	O
nghiêm	O
túc	O
trong	O
công	O
viêc	O
Tiếng	O
Anh	O
Có	O
khả	O
năng	O
giao	O
tiếp	O
và	O
đọc	O
hiểu	O
tài	O
liệu	O
TOEIC	B-SOFT_SKILL
Nghe	O
Đọc:	O
825	O
.	O

Experience	O
Teaching	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
-	O
Sumato	B-ORG
Academy	I-ORG
May	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
May	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
○	O
Courses:	O
Lego	O
Wedo,	O
Python	O
Basic,	O
Robotics.	O
Collaborated	O
with	O
other	O
TAs	O
and	O
teachers	O
to	O
design	O
curriculum	O
for	O
kids.	O
○	O
.	O

-	O
By	O
offline	O
evaluation,	O
the	O
model	O
can	O
fit	O
the	O
preference's	O
users	O
with	O
the	O
result	O
of	O
hit	O
ratio	O
metric	O
is	O
up	O
to	O
0.95.	O
.Technologies:	O
-	O
Language:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
PyTorch	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
DDPG	B-TECH_SKILL
model,	O
DQN	B-TECH_SKILL
model,	O
Kmeans	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
❖	O
FPT	B-ORG
Smart	I-ORG
Cloud	I-ORG
August	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
August	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
-	O
Design	O
and	O
training	O
AI	O
model	O
applied	O
in	O
company	O
product	O
❖	O
Global	B-ORG
Smart	I-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG
August	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
-	O
Design	O
and	O
training	O
AI	O
model	O
applied	O
in	O
company	O
product	O
.	O

•	O
Learning	O
about	O
business	O
problem	O
thinking.	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
•	O
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Greenwich	I-ORG
VietNam	I-ORG
(Grad:	O
Dec	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
)	O
•	O
Major:	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.5/10	I-SCORE
.	O

·	O
Work	O
on	O
computer	O
vision	O
ﬁelds:	O
Classiﬁcation,	O
object	B-TECH_SKILL
detection	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
ocr	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
...	O
·	O
Have	O
exprienced	O
on	O
MLops	B-TECH_SKILL
:	O
Docker	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Linux	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
AWS	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

-	O
Framework:	O
Tensorﬂow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
09/2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
06/2023	I-TIME
Arti�cial	B-ORG
Intelligence	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
UIT	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
Member	B-POSITION
of	I-POSITION
Machine	I-POSITION
Learning	I-POSITION
Team	I-POSITION
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Information	B-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
Department	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
VNU	I-ORG
08/2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
,	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.22	I-SCORE
.	O

	O
Work	O
Experience	O
DR	B-ORG
COM	I-ORG
JULY	B-TIME
2014	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
SEPTEMBER	I-TIME
2014	I-TIME
Tester	B-POSITION
-	I-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
-	O
Track	O
bugs	O
and	O
error	O
of	O
programs	O
from	O
developer	O
and	O
report	O
to	O
developing	O
team	O
-	O
Make	O
reports	O
of	O
bug	O
tracking	O
every	O
day.	O
Achievements	O
and	O
skills	O
gained:	O
-	O
Gain	O
experience	O
from	O
working	O
in	O
oﬃcial	O
environment.	O
-	O
Observe,	O
learn	O
how	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
team	O
and	O
new	O
skills.	O
-	O
Improve	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
Communication	I-SOFT_SKILL
Skill	I-SOFT_SKILL
TMA	B-ORG
SOLUTION	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
TMA	I-ORG
INNOVATION	I-ORG
CENTER	I-ORG
SEPTEMBER	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
MAY	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
Business	B-POSITION
Analyst	I-POSITION
-	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
-	I-POSITION
Data	I-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
-	I-POSITION
AI	I-POSITION
Researcher	I-POSITION
-	I-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
-	O
Do	O
the	O
R&D	O
Project	O
for	O
graduation	O
from	O
University	O
-	O
Project:	O
Intelligence	O
Personalized	O
Learning	O
System	O
-	O
Obligation:	O
+	O
Be	O
responsible	O
for	O
the	O
requirement	O
document	O
+	O
Research	O
data	O
for	O
the	O
Information	O
System	O
+	O
Work	O
on	O
creating	O
and	O
developing	O
algorithms	O
and	O
functions	O
to	O
run	O
the	O
system	O
.	O

HUYNH	B-NAME
DUC	I-NAME
THANG	I-NAME
.	O

Education	O
•	O
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh,	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
B.Sc.	B-DEGREE
in	O
Artiﬁcial	B-MAJOR
Intelligence	I-MAJOR
;	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.32/10	I-SCORE
;	O
Full	O
Tuition	O
Scholarship	O
Sep	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Apr	I-TIME
2024	I-TIME
(expected)	O
•	O
Nguyen	B-ORG
Thuong	I-ORG
Hien	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
,	O
Vietnam	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.8/10	I-SCORE
Sep	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Aug	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
.	O

.	O

ACADEMIC	O
LEVEL	O
•	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
.	O

NGUYỄN	B-NAME
TRÍ	I-NAME
QUÂN	I-NAME
AI	B-POSITION
Residency	I-POSITION
.	O

HỌC	O
VẤN	O
09/2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
03/2022	I-TIME
Đại	B-ORG
học	I-ORG
Bách	I-ORG
Khoa	I-ORG
Hà	I-ORG
Nội	I-ORG
Viện	I-ORG
Điện	I-ORG
Tử	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
Viễn	I-ORG
Thông	I-ORG
Thesis:	O
Masked	O
face	O
detection	O
by	O
Deep	O
Learning	O
using	O
Asian	O
face	O
dataset.	O
CPA	B-SCORE
2.49/4.0	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
❖	O
DucPho	B-ORG
No.1	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
❖	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Science	O
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
Expected	O
Nov	B-TIME
2023	I-TIME
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.44/4.0	I-SCORE
.	O

GENERAL	O
INFORMATION	O
●	O
Mobile:	O
+61	B-PHONE
452554720	I-PHONE
●	O
Email:	O
ddnhanau@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
Github:	O
https://github.com/DoDucNhan	O
●	O
.	O

Work	O
Experience	O
Marketing	B-POSITION
Manager	I-POSITION
,	O
Mobagel	B-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.,	O
Mountain	O
View,	O
CA	O
Jun	B-TIME
2015	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Sep	I-TIME
2016	I-TIME
-	O
Responsible	O
for	O
U.S.	O
market	O
outbound	O
marketing.	O
Reported	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
CEO.	O
-	O
Built	O
and	O
operated	O
end-to-end	O
outbound	O
marketing	O
pipeline	O
to	O
generate	O
and	O
deliver	O
200-300	O
emails	O
per	O
week	O
to	O
potential	O
prospects.	O
Achieved	O
86%	O
conversion	O
rate.	O
-	O
Managed	O
team	O
up	O
to	O
10	O
members	O
including	O
interns	O
and	O
contractors.	O
Marketing	B-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
,	O
Magpie	B-ORG
Lab	I-ORG
Inc	I-ORG
.,	O
San	B-LOC
Francisco,	I-LOC
CA	I-LOC
Feb	B-TIME
2015	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Jun	I-TIME
2015	I-TIME
-	O
Responsible	O
for	O
generating	O
leads	O
and	O
growth	O
of	O
user-base.	O
Achieved	O
70%	O
conversion	O
rate.	O
.	O

WORKING	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Research	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
at	O
CTARG	B-ORG
Lab	I-ORG
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Communications	O
Theory	O
and	O
Applications	O
Research	O
Group	O
·	O
Work	O
on	O
projects	O
related	O
to	O
reliable	O
transmission	O
for	O
Underwater	O
Optical	O
Wireless	O
Communication	O
and	O
multiple	O
access	O
protocols.	O
·	O
Use	O
Markov	O
chain	O
model	O
to	O
analyze	O
performances	O
of	O
the	O
system.	O
.	O

My	O
major	O
is	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Vision	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.81/10	I-SCORE
Võ	B-ORG
Nguyên	I-ORG
Giáp	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
2017-2020	B-TIME
I	O
am	O
a	O
former	O
student	O
majoring	O
in	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
at	O
Vo	B-ORG
Nguyen	I-ORG
Giap	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.8/10	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Chung-Ang	B-ORG
University,	I-ORG
South	I-ORG
Korea	I-ORG
MASTER	B-DEGREE
OF	I-DEGREE
ENGINEERING	I-DEGREE
•	O
Department:	O
Computer	O
Science	O
and	O
Engineering.	O
•	O
Major:	O
Big	B-MAJOR
Data	I-MAJOR
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Kien	B-ORG
Tuong	I-ORG
Highschool	I-ORG
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Student	O
-	O
GPA	B-SCORE
9.8	I-SCORE
Graduated	O
as	O
valedictorian	O
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
present	I-TIME
Studying	O
Artificial	B-MAJOR
Intelligence	I-MAJOR
Current	O
GPA	B-SCORE
9.32/10	I-SCORE
.	O

Education	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineer	I-MAJOR
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
now	I-TIME
|	O
A	O
student	O
of	O
Can	B-ORG
Tho	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.18	I-SCORE
.	O

SKILLS	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
3/5	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
3/5	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
learning	I-TECH_SKILL
3/5	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Keras	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Colab	O
3/5	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
3/5	O
.	O

I	O
also	O
helped	O
in	O
debugging	O
a	O
stock	O
trading	O
app.	O
.	O

Work	O
Experience	O
04/09/2019–09/12/2019	B-TIME
Intern•	B-POSITION
Front-End	I-POSITION
•	O
User	O
Experience	O
Researchers.	O
I	O
was	O
assigned	O
to	O
re-create	O
the	O
Kanban	O
board	O
(Trello-like,	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
chance	O
to	O
know	O
about	O
web	O
development.	O
I	O
also	O
learned	O
so	O
much	O
about	O
the	O
process	O
of	O
working	O
and	O
creating	O
a	O
product	O
and	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
real-world	O
project.	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
❖	O
HCMC	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Education	I-ORG
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Mechatronics	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
Technology	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.05/4	I-SCORE
❖	O
Kon	B-ORG
Tum	I-ORG
Nguyen	I-ORG
Tat	I-ORG
Thanh	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
2013	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
Physics	B-MAJOR
class	I-MAJOR
-	O
3	O
years	O
as	O
class	O
president	O
-	O
Third	O
Prize	O
in	O
Provincial	O
Physics	O
Exam	O
2017	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
2015	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Le	B-ORG
Quy	I-ORG
Don	I-ORG
Machine	O
Learning	O
Engineer	O
Nanodegree	O
Highschool	O
for	O
the	O
gifted	O
CS229:	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Bach	B-ORG
Khoa	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Deep	O
Learning	O
Nanodegree	O
CS230:	O
Deep	O
Learning	O
.	O

SKILL	O
·	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
·	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
·	O
Linear	O
Algebra	O
·	O
Reinforcement	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
·	O
Statistics	O
&	O
Probability	O
·	O
Intermediate	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
·	O
Data	O
structure	O
&	O
Algorithm	O
.	O

Researching	O
and	O
building	O
the	O
optic	O
macula	O
and	O
disc	O
object	O
detection	O
by	O
Detetron2	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
Teaching	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
for	O
AI	O
for	O
Healthcare	O
course	O
at	O
International	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
|	O
09/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
now	I-TIME
.	O

SKILLS	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
Programming	O
Language	O
English	O
document	O
translation	O
MATLAB	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Responsibilities	O
Write	O
Tutorials	O
for	O
Club	O
Website.	O
Collect	O
Datasets	O
and	O
Organize	O
AI	O
Challenge	O
2020	O
Competition.	O
Hosting	O
discussion	O
seminar	O
on	O
AI	O
weekly.	O
Technologies:	O
Google	B-TECH_SKILL
Collaboratory	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Latex	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Docker	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
labelImg	B-TECH_SKILL
,...	O
01/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
06/2021	I-TIME
Computer	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
Media	I-ORG
Marketing	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
Vice	B-POSITION
Leader	I-POSITION
,	O
Designer	B-POSITION
,	O
Content	B-POSITION
Marker	I-POSITION
.	O

WORKING	O
EXPERIENCE	O
BIZ4	B-ORG
TECHNOLOGY	I-ORG
CO.,	I-ORG
LTD	I-ORG
APRIL	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
AUGUST	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
Using	O
the	O
Xamarin	O
technology	O
of	O
the	O
C#	B-TECH_SKILL
language	O
together	O
with	O
the	O
.Net	B-TECH_SKILL
framework	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
short	O
or	O
long	O
term	O
time	O
and	O
schedule	O
management	O
application.	O
The	O
next	O
project	O
deploys	O
the	O
company's	O
internal	O
employee	O
management	O
application,	O
including	O
features	O
such	O
as	O
time	O
attendance,	O
approval	O
application,	O
progress	O
reporting,	O
division	O
of	O
work	O
of	O
each	O
department,	O
etc.,	O
developed	O
on	O
the	O
Android	O
platform.	O
FPT	B-ORG
SOFTWARE	I-ORG
CO.,	I-ORG
LTD	I-ORG
SEPTEMBER	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
NOVEMBER	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
INTERSHIP	B-POSITION
Lasting	O
2	O
months	O
internship	O
at	O
the	O
Company,	O
of	O
which	O
1	O
month	O
used	O
SQLite	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
and	O
trained	O
in	O
both	O
HTML5	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
CSS3	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Tran	B-NAME
Hoang	I-NAME
Khuong	I-NAME
.	O

.	O

EDUCATION	O
Oct	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
June	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
-	I-ORG
VNU	I-ORG
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
Coursera.org	O
Machine	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Deep	B-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
Specialization	O
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCES	O
TMA	B-ORG
Innovation	I-ORG
Dec	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Dec	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
-	O
Part-time	O
•	O
Working	O
and	O
improving	O
deep	O
learning	O
model	O
for	O
object	O
detection	O
and	O
object	O
segmentation.	O
•	O
Image	O
processing	O
with	O
OpenCV	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

LANGUAGE:	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
:	O
IELTS	O
8.0	O
German	B-SOFT_SKILL
:	O
A2	O
Vietnamese	B-SOFT_SKILL
:	O
Native	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
Advanced	O
Program	O
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science,	I-MAJOR
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
city	I-ORG
Univer-	I-ORG
sity	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
�	O
Sep	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Sep	I-TIME
2023	I-TIME
�	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
city,	I-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.97/4.00	I-SCORE
High	B-ORG
School	I-ORG
Phan	I-ORG
Ngoc	I-ORG
Hien	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	O
Gifted	O
Students	O
�	O
Sep	B-TIME
2016	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Jun	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
�	O
Ca	B-LOC
Mau	I-LOC
city,	I-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
•	O
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
Class	O
.	O

Other	O
research	O
projects	O
Vietnamese	O
Spelling	O
Error	O
Detection	O
October	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
Computational	O
Linguistics	O
Center	O
&	O
Knowledge	O
Engineering	O
department,	O
HCMUS	O
•	O
Authors:	O
Nguyen	O
Hoang-Gia	O
and	O
Pham	O
Bao-Duy	O
•	O
Using	O
Laplace-smoothed	O
Bi-gram	O
method	O
to	O
detect	O
errors	O
in	O
Vietnamese	O
text.	O
Human	O
Hand	O
Action	O
Detection	O
for	O
Indirect	O
Controller	O
April	O
2019	O
Smart	O
Environment	O
Laboratory,	O
HCMUS	O
•	O
Authors:	O
Nguyen	O
Hoang-Gia,	O
Trang-Phuong	O
N.	O
Nguyen,	O
and	O
Le	O
Dinh	O
Anh-Duy	O
•	O
Real	O
time	O
tracking	O
hand	O
actions	O
using	O
pre-trained	O
CNN	O
model.	O
.	O

Phone	O
(+84)	B-NAME
905-198-999	I-NAME
Email	O
phamhoangbao2000@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
.	O

Lawrence	B-ORG
S.Ting	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
–	O
Ho	O
Chi	O
Minh	O
City	O
Vietnam	O
|	O
High	O
School	O
Diploma	O
12/2016	B-TIME
•	O
Lawrence	O
S.Ting	O
School	O
Entrance	O
Scholarship	O
2014	O
Recipient.	O
.	O

Education	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
–	O
Final	O
year	O
Student	O
(	O
9/2017-	B-TIME
9/2021	I-TIME
)	O
	O
Major:	O
Control	B-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
automation	I-MAJOR
	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.29/10	I-SCORE
(Expected	O
to	O
be	O
8.43/10	O
by	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
graduation)	O
	O
English:	O
TOEIC	B-SOFT_SKILL
980/990	O
	O
Student	O
of	O
the	O
honor	O
class	O
	O
Research	O
experiences:	O
	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
System	O
for	O
Reading	O
Analog	O
Gauges	O
at	O
Power	O
Substation	O
(Published	O
at	O
ISEE	O
2021	O
DOI:	O
https://doi.org/10.1109/ISEE51682.2021.9418754)	O
	O
A	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
System	O
for	O
Power	O
Transmission	O
Line	O
Inspection	O
Robot	O
(Published	O
at	O
ICSSE	O
2021	O
DOI:	O
https://doi.org/10.1109/ICSSE52999.2021.9538440)	O
	O
Body	O
Temperature	O
and	O
Facemask	O
Identification	O
Using	O
Cameras	O
(Presented	O
at	O
“The	O
8th	O
Science	O
and	O
Technology	O
Symposium	O
for	O
OISP	O
Students”)	O
.	O

Skills	O
Mathematics	O
Formerly	O
majored	O
in	O
mathematics.	O
Good	O
logical	B-SOFT_SKILL
thinking	I-SOFT_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
B.S	B-DEGREE
.	O

Bach	B-LOC
Khoa	I-LOC
Dormitory,	I-LOC
District	I-LOC
10,	I-LOC
HCMC	I-LOC
(+84)	B-PHONE
38	I-PHONE
889	I-PHONE
4615	I-PHONE
danglinh.anh000@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
www.linkedin.com/in/anhdang000	O
www.github.com/anhdang000	O
.	O

HUNG-VO	B-NAME
TRAN	I-NAME
CHI	I-NAME
.	O

June	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Ongoing	I-TIME
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
AI	B-POSITION
lab	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
•	O
Supported	O
writing	O
thesis,	O
conduct	O
experiment,	O
clean	O
and	O
visualize	O
data.	O
June	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Ongoing	I-TIME
Pay	B-ORG
It	I-ORG
Forward	I-ORG
Club	I-ORG
Leader	B-SCORE
•	O
Organize	O
basic	O
electronic	O
and	O
micro	O
controller	O
training	O
class	O
for	O
student,	O
specific	O
the	O
STM32	B-TECH_SKILL
microcontroller	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
BACKGROUND	O
Denison	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Granville,	I-ORG
Ohio	I-ORG
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
sciences	I-DEGREE
,	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
science,	I-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Mathematics	I-MAJOR
Expected	O
Graduation:	O
May	B-TIME
2025	I-TIME
.	O

Minh	B-NAME
Quan	I-NAME
Dao	I-NAME
Curriculum	O
Vitae	O
Contact	O
Information	O
Email:	O
kevinquandao10@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
Phone:	O
0385719921	B-PHONE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
2019	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
HCMC	I-ORG
•	O
Major:	O
Artiﬁcial	B-MAJOR
Intelligence	I-MAJOR
,	O
ﬁnal-year	O
student	O
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
9.2/10	I-SCORE
.	O

Phone	O
Number:	O
0337189900	B-PHONE
Email:	O
thai.dec1mo@gmail.com	B-EMAIL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
High	O
school	O
Aug.	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
July	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Phan	B-ORG
Boi	I-ORG
Chau	I-ORG
high	I-ORG
school	I-ORG
for	O
gifted	O
student	O
Nghe	O
An,	O
Vietnam	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	I-DEGREE
Science	I-DEGREE
|	O
Major:	O
Electrical	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
Aug.	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
Vinuniversiy	B-ORG
Hanoi	I-ORG
,	O
Vietnam	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.59	I-SCORE
/	I-SCORE
4.0	I-SCORE
.	O

HỌC	O
VẤN	O
Đại	B-ORG
học	I-ORG
Bách	I-ORG
Khoa	I-ORG
Hà	I-ORG
Nội	I-ORG
10/2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Hiện	I-TIME
tại	I-TIME
Chuyên	O
ngành:	O
Khoa	O
học	O
máy	O
tính	O
Hệ:	O
Cao	O
học	O
Đại	B-ORG
học	I-ORG
Bách	I-ORG
Khoa	I-ORG
Hà	I-ORG
Nội	I-ORG
08/2016	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
08/2020	I-TIME
Chuyên	O
ngành:	O
Công	O
nghệ	O
thông	O
tin	O
Tốt	O
nghiệp	O
loại:	O
Xuất	O
sắc	O
.	O

).	O
Misc:	O
Apache	B-TECH_SKILL
Spark	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Apache	B-TECH_SKILL
Hadoop	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
ETL/ELT	B-TECH_SKILL
knowledge.	O
.	O

.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Samsung	B-ORG
Display	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
Innovation	I-ORG
Engineer	B-POSITION
at	O
Inspection	O
Group	O
Jan	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Sep	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	O
Helped	O
management	O
identify	O
workflow	O
issues	O
and	O
find	O
solutions.	O
-	O
Worked	O
as	O
member	O
of	O
a	O
team	O
to	O
create	O
and	O
maintain	O
machines	O
that	O
could	O
function	O
in	O
the	O
absence	O
of	O
human	O
operators,	O
automating	O
various	O
technical	O
tasks.	O
-	O
Innovate	O
the	O
flowchart	O
of	O
Robots,	O
set	O
up	O
an	O
Industrial	O
Visions	O
system.	O
-	O
As	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Inspection	O
group,	O
I	O
also	O
calculate,	O
calibrate	O
the	O
accuracy	O
of	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Visions	I-TECH_SKILL
(	O
COGNEX	B-TECH_SKILL
,..),	O
the	O
result:	O
OK/BAD	O
of	O
products	O
after	O
judgments	O
of	O
both	O
Humans	O
and	O
Computer-programming	O
-	O
Learning	O
and	O
training	O
coding	O
skills	O
(	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
),	O
also	O
ML/DL	O
knowledge	O
overall	O
and	O
applies	O
at	O
own	O
factories	O
at	O
SATEC,	O
an	O
educational	O
center	O
for	O
engineers	O
in	O
Samsung	B-ORG
Display	I-ORG
.	O

Education	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
of	O
Science	O
in	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
,	O
Case	B-ORG
Western	I-ORG
Reserve	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Expected	O
Dec.	B-TIME
2023	I-TIME
•	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.86/4.0	I-SCORE
-	O
Dean’s	O
High	O
Honor	O
List:	O
2020	O
,	O
2021	O
•	O
Courses:	O
Operating	O
Systems,	O
Database	O
Systems,	O
Computer	O
Networks,	O
Data	O
Structures	O
and	O
Algorithms,	O
Web	O
Development,	O
Data	O
Privacy,	O
Data	O
Science,	O
Game	O
Development,	O
C/C++	O
Programming,	O
Number	O
Theory	O
•	O
Activities:	O
Vice	O
President	O
at	O
CWRU	O
Hacker	O
Society,	O
Member	O
at	O
Mathematical	O
Association	O
of	O
America	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Sep	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
May	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Major:	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.5/10	I-SCORE
VietAI	B-ORG
Machine	I-ORG
Learning	I-ORG
Foundation	I-ORG
class	O
May	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
July	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Link:	O
http://vietai.org/	O
Achievement:	O
Distinction	O
level	O
(top	O
10)	O
Le	B-ORG
Quy	I-ORG
Don	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
,	O
Da	O
Nang	O
May	B-TIME
2015	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
May	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
Mathematics	B-MAJOR
specialist	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.8/10	I-SCORE
.	O

EDUCATION	O
Montgomery	B-ORG
College,	I-ORG
Rockville,	I-ORG
MD	I-ORG
Aug	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Major:	O
Computer	B-MAJOR
Science	I-MAJOR
,	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.25/4.0	I-SCORE
,	O
major	O
GPA:3.9/4.0	B-SCORE
-	O
Courses:	O
Calculus,	O
Set	O
Theory,	O
Linear	O
Algebra,	O
Biostatistics,	O
Mathematics	O
for	O
Machine	O
Learning,	O
Competitive	O
Programming,	O
Object	B-TECH_SKILL
Oriented	I-TECH_SKILL
Programming	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Research	O
Experience	O
Undergraduate	B-POSITION
Research	I-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
June	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Dec.	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Network	B-ORG
Science	I-ORG
&	I-ORG
Optimization	I-ORG
Lab.,	I-ORG
Dept.	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Systems	I-ORG
Engineering,	I-ORG
CUHK	I-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
•	O
Advisor:	O
Prof.	O
Hoi-To	O
Wai	O
•	O
Proposed	O
a	O
novel	O
research	O
direction	O
for	O
theoretical	O
analysis	O
of	O
current	O
graph	B-TECH_SKILL
neural	I-TECH_SKILL
network	I-TECH_SKILL
models	O
•	O
Provided	O
mathematical	O
proofs	O
for	O
a	O
new	O
stability	O
bound	O
of	O
graph	O
neural	O
networks	O
subject	O
to	O
large	O
random	O
perturbations,	O
using	O
tools	O
from	O
graph	O
signal	O
procesing	O
and	O
random	O
matrix	O
theory	O
•	O
Designed	O
numerical	O
experiments	O
on	O
large	O
real-world	O
datasets	O
using	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
to	O
support	O
theoretical	O
results	O
Undergraduate	B-POSITION
Research	I-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
June	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Aug.	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
Husky	B-ORG
Lab.,	I-ORG
Dept.	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Computer	I-ORG
Science,	I-ORG
CUHK	I-ORG
Hong	I-ORG
Kong	I-ORG
•	O
Advisor:	O
Prof.	O
James	O
Cheng	O
•	O
Conducted	O
an	O
in-depth	O
literature	O
review	O
on	O
current	O
state-of-the-art	O
graph	O
neural	O
networks	O
•	O
Performed	O
extensive	O
simulations	O
using	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Maxima	B-TECH_SKILL
to	O
analyze	O
the	O
performances	O
of	O
various	O
machine	O
learning	O
models	O
for	O
graph	O
data	O
.	O

NGUYEN	B-NAME
TRONG	I-NAME
VAN	I-NAME
.	O

•	O
Time:	O
Oct	B-TIME
2014	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Nov	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
.	O

SKILLS	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
Deep	I-TECH_SKILL
Learning	I-TECH_SKILL
for	O
Computer	B-TECH_SKILL
Vision	I-TECH_SKILL
Communication	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
Academics	O
English	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
&	I-TECH_SKILL
OOP	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Education	O
Bachelor	B-DEGREE
,	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
,	O
Ho	B-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2022	I-TIME
Major:	O
Software	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
3.77/4	I-SCORE
School-level	O
"ﬁve-good	O
student"	O
Class	O
Secretary	O
.	O

SKILLS	O
Programming	O
language	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C/C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C#	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
HTML5/CSS3	B-TECH_SKILL
Tool,	O
Library,	O
Framework	O
TensorFlow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
OpenCV	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Scipy	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Numpy	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pandas	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Matplotlib	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tesseract	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SkLearn	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Django	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Beautiful	B-TECH_SKILL
Soup	I-TECH_SKILL
4,	O
etc.	O
Data	O
Science	O
Mathematics,	O
Statistics,	O
Machine	O
Learning	O
-	O
Deep	O
Learning	O
with	O
hands	O
on	O
experience	O
of	O
Tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
Basic	O
Other	O
Experience	O
with	O
Git	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Communication	B-SOFT_SKILL
,	O
Teamwork	B-SOFT_SKILL
.	O

SKILLS	O
Programming	O
Language	O
C/C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Java	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Matlab	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
JavaScript	B-TECH_SKILL
Languages	O
Vietnamese	B-SOFT_SKILL
,	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
(685	O
Toeic	O
in	O
HUST	O
intenal	O
test)	O
Technical	O
Skills	O
PyTorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
TensorFlow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
TensorRT	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
ROS	B-TECH_SKILL
Database	O
MongoDB	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Mysql	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

KEY	O
SKILLS	O
Communication	B-SOFT_SKILL
skills	O
Time	B-SOFT_SKILL
management	I-SOFT_SKILL
skills	O
Problem	B-SOFT_SKILL
Solving	I-SOFT_SKILL
Machine	I-SOFT_SKILL
Vision	I-SOFT_SKILL
Natural	I-SOFT_SKILL
Language	I-SOFT_SKILL
Processing	I-SOFT_SKILL
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
FTECH	B-ORG
CO.,	I-ORG
LTD	I-ORG
Web	B-POSITION
Backend	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Jul	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Sep	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Learnt	O
how	O
to	O
put	O
knowledge	O
into	O
practice	O
to	O
work	O
in	O
a	O
professional	O
ofﬁce	O
environment	O
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
April2020	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Ha	B-ORG
Noi	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG
Industry	I-ORG
Resercher	I-ORG
in	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Lab	I-ORG
Main	O
responsibilities:	O
-Reserch	O
and	O
implementation	O
about	O
Computer	O
Vison	O
and	O
Deep	O
Learning,Machine	O
Learning	O
application	O
-Reserch	O
and	O
implementation	O
about	O
Internet	O
Of	O
Things	O
application	O
Recognition	O
and	O
Gains:	O
-	O
PID	O
Motor	O
DC	O
Controlled	O
with	O
ARM	O
STM32F4	O
and	O
ESP8266	O
.	O

Programming	O
skill	O
Programming	O
language:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
Numpy	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pandas	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Matplotlib	B-TECH_SKILL
:	O
-	O
Knowledge	O
about	O
data	O
science	O
library	O
-	O
Course:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
for	O
DataScience	O
(freeCodeCamp)	O
Machine	O
Learning:	O
-	O
Basic	O
algorithms:	O
Linear	O
Regression,	O
SVM	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
KNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,...	O
-	O
Blog:	O
machinelearningcoban.com	O
-	O
Course:	O
Machine	O
learning	O
(CS229N),	O
Machine	O
learning	O
with	O
graphs	O
(CS224W,	O
Stanford)	O
Deep	O
Learning:	O
-	O
Neural	B-TECH_SKILL
Network	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
CNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
RNN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
GAN	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
GNN	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Basic	O
knowledge	O
on	O
Computer	O
Vision	O
and	O
Natural	O
Language	O
Processing	O
-	O
Framework:	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tensorﬂow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Keras	B-TECH_SKILL
-	O
Course:	O
NLP	O
Specialization	O
(Coursera),	O
Deep	O
learning	O
cơ	O
bản	O
(AI4E),	O
Natural	O
Language	O
Processing	O
(CS224N)	O
English	B-SOFT_SKILL
:	O
-	O
Toeic:	O
805/990	O
-	O
Good	O
communication	B-SOFT_SKILL
,	O
reading	O
and	O
listening	O
skill	O
.	O

Tuan	B-NAME
Anh	I-NAME
Le	I-NAME
39/29/3	B-LOC
Hoang	I-LOC
Bat	I-LOC
Dat	I-LOC
street,	I-LOC
Ho	I-LOC
Chi	I-LOC
Minh	I-LOC
City	I-LOC
700000,	O
VN	O
Phone:	O
(077)	B-PHONE
876	I-PHONE
8582	I-PHONE
|Email:	O
tuanle_2024@depauw.edu	B-EMAIL
LinkedIn:	O
linkedin.com/in/le-tuan-02b062199/	O
.	O

TECHNICAL	O
SKILLS	O
●	O
Proficient:	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
C++	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Darknet	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tensorflow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
AWS	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
GCP	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Azure	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
LaTeX	B-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
Intern	B-POSITION
Arrow	B-ORG
Technologies	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
Jun	B-TIME
2020-Sep	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
•	O
Drone	O
Solar	O
Panel	O
Inspection	O
o	O
Use	O
open-CV	B-TECH_SKILL
library	O
to	O
detect	O
single	O
panel	O
from	O
solar	O
farm	O
images	O
captured	O
by	O
drone.	O
Convert	O
thermal	O
panel	O
images	O
to	O
gray	O
panel	O
images	O
for	O
classification	O
task.	O
o	O
.	O

	O
SKILLS	O
AND	O
TECHNIQUES	O
Python	B-TECH_SKILL
for	O
Data	O
Science	O
Can	O
use	O
Numpy	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pandas	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Matplotlib	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
sci-kit	B-TECH_SKILL
learn	I-TECH_SKILL
for	O
Data	B-TECH_SKILL
Visualization	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

Quyen	B-NAME
Tran	I-NAME
Email	O
·	O
Github	O
·	O
Linkedin	O
Hanoi,	O
VietNam	O
.	O

I	O
worked	O
with	O
a	O
team	O
of	O
six	O
people	O
and	O
we	O
used	O
.NET	B-TECH_SKILL
MVC	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

.	O

.	O

.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
AI	B-POSITION
Internship	I-POSITION
Aug	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
NOW	I-TIME
Tima	B-ORG
Group	I-ORG
Corporation	I-ORG
Research	O
and	O
develop	O
credit	O
scoring	O
problems	O
in	O
Vietnam	O
with	O
charac-	O
teristics	O
of	O
a	O
startup	O
company.	O
•	O
Analysis	O
and	O
process	O
data	O
•	O
Research	O
solution	O
for	O
this	O
problem	O
•	O
Deployed	O
projects	O
from	O
existing	O
backgrounds	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
from	O
the	O
experi-	O
ence	O
of	O
research	O
groups	O
Technologies	O
include:	O
•	O
Framework	O
and	O
library:	O
Sklearn	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Tensorlfow	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Numpy	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Pandas	B-TECH_SKILL
,etc	O
•	O
IDE:	O
Google	B-TECH_SKILL
Colab	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Visual	B-TECH_SKILL
studio	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
etc	O
•	O
Other	O
Tools:	O
SQL	B-TECH_SKILL
Server	I-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Postman	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
Git	B-TECH_SKILL
,etc	O
Achievements	O
include:	O
•	O
Apply	O
knowledge	O
to	O
complete	O
and	O
put	O
the	O
project	O
to	O
practice	O
•	O
Good	O
label	O
correct	O
prediction	O
rate	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
95	O
•	O
AUC	O
score	O
is	O
more	O
than	O
0.74	O
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Junior	B-POSITION
Mobile	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
April	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Telecom	I-ORG
—	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
•	O
Building	O
apps	O
on	O
iOS	O
using	O
Swift.	O
•	O
Projects:	O
–	O
Hi	O
FPT:	O
an	O
app	O
for	O
customers	O
view	O
and	O
manage	O
services,	O
over	O
2	O
millions	O
users.	O
–	O
Hi	O
Opennet:	O
an	O
app	O
for	O
Khmer	O
customers.	O
Intern	B-POSITION
Mobile	I-POSITION
Developer	I-POSITION
April	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
March	I-TIME
2020	I-TIME
FPT	B-ORG
Telecom	I-ORG
—	I-ORG
Ho	I-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
City	I-ORG
•	O
Learning	O
and	O
implementing	O
design	O
patterns,	O
object	B-TECH_SKILL
oriented	I-TECH_SKILL
programming	I-TECH_SKILL
.	O

EDUCATION	O
September	B-TIME
2018	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Ha	B-ORG
Noi	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
Of	I-ORG
Industry	I-ORG
Major:	O
Control	B-MAJOR
Engineering	I-MAJOR
and	I-MAJOR
Automation	I-MAJOR
GPA:	B-SCORE
2.62/4	I-SCORE
.	O

.	O

EXPERIENCE	O
Wisdom	B-ORG
Robotics	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
,	O
remote	B-POSITION
Trainee	I-POSITION
March	B-TIME
2022	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
•	O
Being	O
trained	O
and	O
working	O
in	O
a	O
project	O
to	O
create	O
a	O
chatbot	O
for	O
educational	O
purpose	O
•	O
Discussing	O
with	O
customers	O
about	O
the	O
function	O
and	O
progress	O
of	O
the	O
projects	O
Department	O
of	O
Mathematics	O
and	O
Statistic,	O
Tampa	B-ORG
,	O
FL	B-POSITION
Peer	I-POSITION
Leader	I-POSITION
in	O
Calculus	O
I	O
January	B-TIME
2022	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Now	I-TIME
•	O
Managing	O
Peer	O
Leading	O
section	O
•	O
Developing	O
discussions	O
and	O
crictical	O
thinking	O
.	O

EDUCATION	O
2018	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
:	O
-	O
Student	O
at	O
Hanoi	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Science	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
(HUST)	I-ORG
-	O
Excellent	O
Engineer	O
Training	O
Program	O
(PFIEV)	O
Specialty:	O
Information	O
and	O
Communication	O
Systems	O
Average	O
mark	O
of	O
the	O
6	O
semesters:	O
9.27/10	O
(in	O
credit:	O
3.71/4	B-SCORE
).	O
2015	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2018	I-TIME
:	O
-	O
Elite	O
class	O
of	O
Nguyen	B-ORG
Tat	I-ORG
Thanh	I-ORG
high	I-ORG
school	I-ORG
-	O
Hanoi	B-LOC
.	O

WORK	O
EXPERIENCE	O
Part-time	B-POSITION
Staﬀ	I-POSITION
FUVITECH	B-ORG
CO.,LTD	I-ORG
12/2021	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
02/2021	I-TIME
,	O
Tasks	O
Manage	O
and	O
test	O
electronic	O
components.	O
Customer	O
service	O
and	O
support.	O
.	O

Working	O
Experience	O
Embedded	B-POSITION
Software	I-POSITION
Intern	I-POSITION
Robert	B-ORG
Bosch	I-ORG
Engineering	I-ORG
and	I-ORG
Business	I-ORG
Solutions	I-ORG
Vietnam	I-ORG
Co.,	I-ORG
Ltd	I-ORG
.	O

Experience	O
VinBrain	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
Vingroup	I-ORG
May.	B-TIME
2021	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Applied	B-POSITION
Scientist	I-POSITION
•	O
Participate	O
in	O
AI	O
development	O
projects	O
for	O
medical	O
segmentation	O
and	O
diagnostic	O
imaging	O
products	O
and	O
Smart	O
City	O
3D	O
MRI	O
Image	O
CT-Rectal	O
Tumor	O
Segmentation	O
∗	O
Proposed	O
and	O
develop	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
combining	O
a	O
decode-part	O
of	O
U-Net	B-TECH_SKILL
with	O
a	O
Transformer	B-TECH_SKILL
-part	O
and	O
tow	O
decoder-part	O
of	O
VAE-net	B-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Seg-net	O
for	O
the	O
problem	O
of	O
3	O
D	O
MRI	O
Image	O
segmentation	O
pixel	O
level	O
for	O
tumor-part.	O
∗	O
Analysis,	O
processing	O
and	O
visualization	O
Dataset	O
∗	O
Support	O
and	O
collaborate	O
with	O
the	O
web	O
backend	O
development	O
team	O
to	O
deloy	O
the	O
trained	O
AI	O
model	O
to	O
the	O
AWS	O
cloud	O
server	O
and	O
Web	O
service	O
∗	O
Framework:	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
OpenCV	B-TECH_SKILL
Coverface	O
detection	O
on	O
surveillance	O
camera	O
-	O
SmartCity	O
∗	O
Develop	O
a	O
Yolo	B-TECH_SKILL
model	O
to	O
detection	O
Coverface	O
∗	O
Analysis,	O
processing	O
and	O
visualization	O
Dataset	O
∗	O
Support	O
and	O
collaborate	O
with	O
the	O
web	O
backend	O
development	O
team	O
to	O
deloy	O
the	O
trained	O
AI	O
model	O
to	O
the	O
AWS	B-TECH_SKILL
cloud	I-TECH_SKILL
server	I-TECH_SKILL
and	O
Web	O
service	O
∗	O
Framework:	O
Pytorch	B-TECH_SKILL
,	O
OpenCV	B-TECH_SKILL
MMLab	B-ORG
-	I-ORG
UIT	I-ORG
Oct.	B-TIME
2019	I-TIME
–	I-TIME
Present	I-TIME
Research	B-POSITION
Assistant	I-POSITION
University	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Information	I-ORG
Technology-VNUHCM	I-ORG
•	O
Topic	O
research:	O
Violence	O
detection	O
in	O
video	O
surveillance	O
based	O
on	O
the	O
approach	O
of	O
Deep	O
Multiple	O
Instance	O
Learning	O
Ranking	O
PDF	O
•	O
Advisor:	O
Duy-Dinh	O
Le	O
FPT	B-ORG
Software	I-ORG
May.2020	B-TIME
–	I-TIME
May.	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
AI	B-POSITION
Engineer	I-POSITION
Hochiminh,	B-LOC
Vietnam	I-LOC
Semantic	O
Segmentation	O
for	O
Teeth	O
dental	O
X-Ray	O
•	O
Proposed	O
and	O
Develop	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
combining	O
U-Net	B-TECH_SKILL
with	O
LSTM/RNN	B-TECH_SKILL
for	O
the	O
problem	O
of	O
segmentation	O
pixel	O
level	O
for	O
each	O
Tooth	O
of	O
the	O
X-Ray	O
images	O
.	O

Leadership	B-POSITION
and	I-POSITION
Teaching	I-POSITION
Experience	O
Oct	B-TIME
2020	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Jan	I-TIME
2021	I-TIME
Electronic	O
class	O
for	O
students	O
Leader	O
•	O
Organized	O
and	O
taught	O
the	O
Basic	O
Electronic	O
and	O
STM32	O
microcontroller	O
basic	O
coding	O
for	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
students.	O
Jan	B-TIME
2017	I-TIME
-	I-TIME
Feb	I-TIME
2017	I-TIME
Advising	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
Enrollment	I-ORG
Program	I-ORG
Leader	B-POSITION
•	O
Organized	O
the	O
Ho	B-ORG
Chi	I-ORG
Minh	I-ORG
University	I-ORG
of	I-ORG
Technology	I-ORG
advising	O
university	O
enrollment	O
event	O
at	O
Hung	B-ORG
Vuong	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
High	I-ORG
School	I-ORG
..	O
.	O

ACADEMIC	O
HISTORY	O
FPT	B-ORG
University	I-ORG
BACHELOR	B-DEGREE
OF	O
ARTIFICIAL	B-MAJOR
INTELLIGENCE	I-MAJOR
,	O
(	O
2019	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
PRESENT	I-TIME
)	O
GPA:	B-SCORE
8.22	I-SCORE
Tran	B-ORG
Dai	I-ORG
Nghia	I-ORG
Highschool	I-ORG
for	I-ORG
the	I-ORG
Gifted	I-ORG
MATHEMATICS	B-MAJOR
SPECIALIZATION	O
(	O
2017	B-TIME
-	I-TIME
2019	I-TIME
)	O
.	O
